Ranchhod/PERSON Rai/PERSON Patel/PERSON is/O an/O egotistical/O and/O arrogant/O self/O made/O Gujarati/LOCATION man/O who/O arrived/O from/O India/LOCATION and/O settled/O in/O the/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION area/O years/O ago/O ./O 
He/O started/O his/O career/O cleaning/O latrines/O and/O dirty/O clothes/O then/O moved/O on/O to/O working/O in/O a/O restaurant/O saving/O enough/O money/O to/O own/O one/O and/O then/O finally/O owned/O twelve/O ./O 
He/O became/O an/O extremely/O successful/O real/O estate/O magnate/O a/O la/O Donald/PERSON Trump/PERSON and/O was/O so/O big/O headed/O that/O started/O calling/O himself/O THE/O Roger/PERSON Patel/PERSON ./O 
He/O got/O married/O to/O a/O woman/O named/O Kamla/PERSON and/O they/O were/O soon/O proud/O parents/O of/O two/O lovely/O daughters/O Namrata/PERSON and/O Ritu/PERSON ./O 
When/O the/O girls/O are/O grown/O the/O overprotective/O Roger/PERSON arranges/O a/O marriage/O for/O Namrata/PERSON with/O a/O property/O owner/O a/O professional/O Patel/PERSON man/O named/O Prem/PERSON ./O 
Ritu/PERSON Patel/PERSON a/O doctor/O informs/O that/O she/O has/O met/O her/O soul/O mate/O also/O Sunder/PERSON Kapoor/PERSON who/O is/O part/O Punjabi/O and/O part/O Madrasi/PERSON and/O is/O definitely/O not/O a/O Patel/PERSON nor/O a/O property/O owner/O and/O not/O even/O a/O professional/O ./O 
Ambitious/O idealistic/O Stephen/PERSON Chase/PERSON goes/O to/O work/O for/O the/O Atlantis/ORGANIZATION Oil/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION and/O is/O sent/O to/O a/O remote/O outpost/O in/O rural/O China/LOCATION run/O by/O No./O 1/O Boss/O ./O 
After/O a/O while/O he/O feels/O secure/O enough/O to/O send/O for/O his/O fiancee/O and/O goes/O to/O Yokohama/LOCATION to/O meet/O and/O marry/O her/O ./O 
However/O when/O he/O gets/O there/O all/O that/O is/O waiting/O for/O him/O is/O a/O telegram/O in/O which/O she/O explains/O she/O is/O unwilling/O to/O live/O in/O such/O a/O backward/O country/O ./O 
He/O strikes/O up/O a/O conversation/O with/O Hester/PERSON Adams/PERSON ./O 
She/O had/O come/O to/O see/O China/LOCATION for/O the/O first/O time/O with/O her/O father/O a/O professor/O of/O Oriental/O studies/O only/O to/O have/O him/O die/O on/O the/O voyage/O ./O 
As/O they/O become/O better/O acquainted/O Stephen/PERSON comes/O up/O with/O an/O idea/O ./O 
He/O asks/O Hester/PERSON to/O marry/O him/O explaining/O that/O it/O would/O be/O a/O partnership/O ./O 
She/O is/O impressed/O by/O his/O dream/O of/O modernizing/O China/LOCATION and/O accepts/O ./O 
It/O does/O not/O take/O long/O however/O for/O them/O to/O fall/O in/O love/O ./O 
No/O matter/O what/O happens/O nothing/O shakes/O Stephen/PERSON s/O faith/O in/O the/O company/O ./O 
When/O his/O friend/O No./O 1/O Boss/O is/O callously/O transferred/O to/O a/O lesser/O position/O the/O old/O man/O commits/O suicide/O rather/O than/O accept/O the/O insult/O ./O 
The/O new/O boss/O JT/PERSON McCarger/PERSON orders/O Stephen/PERSON to/O man/O an/O even/O more/O isolated/O post/O near/O Siberia/LOCATION ./O 
Stephen/PERSON is/O reluctant/O to/O go/O since/O Hester/PERSON is/O pregnant/O with/O their/O first/O child/O but/O has/O no/O choice/O ./O 
Once/O there/O he/O makes/O the/O agonized/O decision/O to/O go/O deal/O with/O a/O dangerous/O oil/O fire/O rather/O than/O stay/O and/O help/O the/O doctor/O deliver/O the/O baby/O ./O 
When/O he/O returns/O he/O learns/O that/O the/O child/O is/O dead/O ./O 
This/O causes/O a/O temporary/O rift/O between/O him/O and/O his/O wife/O ./O 
Things/O improve/O ./O 
Stephen/PERSON is/O promoted/O and/O assigned/O to/O a/O large/O city/O in/O the/O south/O ./O 
The/O Chases/O becomes/O good/O friends/O with/O another/O couple/O Don/PERSON and/O Alice/PERSON Wellman/PERSON ./O 
Don/PERSON works/O for/O Stephen/PERSON but/O he/O is/O so/O contemptuous/O of/O the/O Chinese/O that/O two/O important/O clients/O refuse/O to/O renew/O their/O contracts/O unless/O he/O is/O fired/O ./O 
Stephen/PERSON is/O torn/O but/O does/O let/O Don/PERSON go/O ./O 
Don/PERSON s/O replacement/O is/O McCarger/PERSON ./O 
Despite/O a/O prolonged/O drought/O and/O an/O outbreak/O of/O cholera/O Stephen/PERSON ruthlessly/O collects/O payment/O from/O his/O customers/O earning/O the/O best/O record/O of/O any/O branch/O in/O China/LOCATION ./O 
Then/O communists/O take/O over/O the/O city/O ./O 
An/O officer/O shows/O up/O at/O the/O company/O s/O offices/O and/O demands/O the/O gold/O stored/O in/O the/O safe/O ./O 
Stephen/PERSON bargains/O with/O him/O and/O gets/O everyone/O except/O McCarger/PERSON and/O himself/O evacuated/O to/O a/O ship/O by/O promising/O to/O give/O up/O the/O gold/O in/O a/O few/O hours/O ./O 
In/O the/O meantime/O he/O sends/O for/O Ho/O a/O very/O well/O connected/O Chinese/O customer/O and/O good/O friend/O hoping/O he/O can/O use/O his/O influence/O ./O 
When/O Ho/PERSON bravely/O shows/O up/O however/O he/O is/O shot/O down/O in/O cold/O blood/O by/O the/O soldiers/O ./O 
Outraged/O Stephen/PERSON and/O McCarger/PERSON take/O the/O gold/O and/O escape/O out/O the/O back/O door/O ./O 
McCarger/PERSON is/O killed/O and/O Stephen/PERSON wounded/O but/O a/O passing/O boat/O rescues/O him/O and/O the/O gold/O ./O 
In/O the/O hospital/O he/O is/O visited/O by/O the/O new/O man/O in/O charge/O of/O the/O Orient/LOCATION for/O the/O company/O ./O 
Stephen/PERSON is/O delighted/O to/O be/O offered/O the/O position/O of/O his/O assistant/O ./O 
However/O when/O his/O boss/O outlines/O his/O plan/O to/O institute/O modern/O business/O practices/O Stephen/PERSON disagrees/O explaining/O that/O despite/O appearances/O the/O new/O China/LOCATION is/O still/O run/O by/O the/O old/O ways/O ./O 
When/O he/O recovers/O he/O is/O humiliated/O to/O learn/O that/O his/O job/O has/O been/O given/O to/O another/O man/O as/O a/O result/O ./O 
Further/O he/O is/O given/O only/O menial/O tasks/O in/O an/O effort/O to/O get/O him/O to/O quit/O ./O 
Hester/PERSON gives/O Stephen/PERSON s/O boss/O a/O tongue/O lashing/O and/O reveals/O that/O her/O husband/O holds/O the/O patent/O for/O a/O lamp/O the/O company/O uses/O to/O popularize/O the/O use/O of/O its/O product/O ./O 
However/O it/O is/O a/O call/O from/O the/O president/O of/O Atlantis/O disturbed/O by/O the/O news/O that/O Stephen/PERSON has/O been/O passed/O over/O for/O the/O job/O that/O changes/O the/O man/O s/O mind/O ./O 
Stephen/PERSON s/O shaken/O faith/O in/O the/O company/O is/O restored/O ./O 
The/O story/O is/O based/O on/O the/O requirement/O of/O Spanish/O land/O owners/O in/O California/LOCATION to/O register/O their/O lands/O before/O a/O deadline/O and/O the/O chicanery/O practiced/O by/O some/O to/O prevent/O registration/O ./O 
Tim/PERSON Kelly/PERSON and/O Max/PERSON Ginsberg/PERSON have/O struck/O it/O rich/O by/O investing/O in/O copper/O stock/O ./O 
But/O when/O the/O stock/O takes/O a/O dive/O they/O are/O compelled/O to/O go/O back/O into/O their/O former/O profession/O junk/O dealers/O ./O 
They/O take/O in/O the/O destitute/O Mary/PERSON Riley/PERSON as/O a/O boarder/O and/O she/O hits/O it/O off/O so/O well/O with/O them/O that/O she/O winds/O up/O becoming/O a/O partner/O in/O their/O rag/O junk/O company/O ./O 
Mary/PERSON falls/O in/O love/O with/O a/O man/O named/O Nathan/PERSON Burke/PERSON the/O son/O of/O wealthy/O parents/O ./O 
Nathan/PERSON s/O mother/O however/O disapproves/O of/O Mary/PERSON ./O 
Eventually/O it/O is/O revealed/O that/O Mrs/PERSON Burke/PERSON came/O from/O a/O poor/O background/O herself/O and/O her/O long/O ago/O sweetheart/O was/O Max/PERSON ./O 
After/O this/O discovery/O she/O gives/O the/O couple/O her/O blessings/O ./O 
The/O copper/O stock/O soars/O in/O value/O once/O again/O so/O Kelly/PERSON and/O Ginsberg/PERSON are/O back/O in/O the/O money.Old/O Clothes/O at/O silentera/O com/O Ben/PERSON Jones/PERSON and/O Marion/PERSON Howdy/PERSON Lewis/PERSON are/O two/O easygoing/O modern/O day/O cowboys/O who/O make/O a/O meager/O living/O breaking/O wild/O horses/O ./O 
Their/O frequent/O employer/O is/O Jim/PERSON Ed/PERSON Love/PERSON a/O shrewd/O businessman/O who/O always/O gets/O the/O better/O of/O them/O ./O 
After/O they/O bring/O him/O a/O string/O of/O tamed/O horses/O and/O spend/O the/O winter/O rounding/O up/O stray/O cows/O he/O talks/O them/O into/O taking/O a/O nondescript/O roan/O horse/O in/O lieu/O of/O some/O of/O their/O wages/O ./O 
Ben/PERSON finds/O that/O the/O horse/O is/O unrideable/O ./O 
Rather/O than/O turning/O it/O into/O soap/O or/O dog/O food/O he/O comes/O up/O with/O the/O bright/O idea/O of/O taking/O it/O to/O a/O rodeo/O and/O betting/O other/O cowhands/O they/O can/O not/O ride/O it/O thereby/O doubling/O their/O earnings/O ./O 
Along/O the/O way/O the/O duo/O stop/O to/O help/O two/O none/O too/O bright/O strippers/O Mary/PERSON and/O Sister/O with/O their/O car/O which/O has/O broken/O down/O ./O 
Not/O knowing/O much/O about/O cars/O they/O give/O them/O a/O ride/O to/O the/O nearest/O garage/O but/O end/O up/O getting/O to/O know/O them/O better/O and/O taking/O them/O along/O to/O the/O rodeo/O ./O 
Everything/O goes/O as/O planned/O nobody/O is/O able/O to/O stay/O on/O the/O horse/O ./O 
Then/O the/O animal/O suddenly/O collapses/O and/O Ben/PERSON spends/O all/O the/O money/O they/O ve/O won/O for/O veterinary/O help/O and/O a/O new/O stable/O to/O replace/O the/O one/O destroyed/O by/O the/O roan/O when/O he/O recovers/O ./O 
In/O the/O end/O Ben/PERSON and/O Howdy/LOCATION end/O up/O right/O back/O where/O they/O started/O with/O only/O the/O roan/O to/O show/O for/O their/O efforts/O ./O 
Fun/O loving/O Bobby/PERSON is/O a/O mail/O clerk/O in/O a/O big/O firm/O but/O he/O has/O a/O trump/O card/O his/O best/O friend/O Waymon/PERSON an/O African/O American/O who/O is/O almost/O a/O partner/O in/O the/O firm/O ./O 
They/O make/O a/O deal/O Waymon/PERSON will/O try/O to/O move/O Bobby/PERSON to/O the/O trainee/O broker/O program/O if/O he/O will/O help/O him/O meet/O Natalie/PERSON the/O girl/O of/O his/O dreams/O ./O 
There/O s/O only/O one/O problem/O everyone/O will/O have/O to/O change/O ./O 
Raj/PERSON Kumar/PERSON is/O an/O honest/O handsome/O and/O intelligent/O young/O man/O to/O boot/O ./O 
He/O works/O as/O a/O sole/O Trader/O therefore/O a/O painter/O by/O trade/O but/O unable/O to/O earn/O a/O living/O and/O unable/O to/O pay/O rent/O to/O his/O kind/O hearted/O but/O talkative/O landlady/O Mrs/O D/O sa/O ./O 
One/O day/O Raj/PERSON finds/O a/O wallet/O containing/O money/O and/O he/O returns/O it/O to/O the/O owner/O Ramnath/PERSON ./O 
Ramnath/PERSON admires/O Raj/PERSON and/O pleased/O with/O his/O honesty/O employs/O him/O to/O work/O in/O his/O office/O as/O a/O Receptionist/O ./O 
Raj/PERSON meets/O with/O Ramnath/PERSON s/O maidservant/O Asha/PERSON and/O soon/O both/O fall/O in/O love/O ./O 
This/O all/O ends/O when/O Raj/PERSON finds/O out/O that/O Asha/PERSON is/O really/O Aarti/O the/O daughter/O of/O his/O employer/O ./O 
He/O then/O alienates/O himself/O from/O his/O employer/O and/O his/O daughter/O and/O looks/O after/O his/O ailing/O landlady/O by/O cooking/O and/O serving/O her/O daily/O meals/O ./O 
Unfortunately/O she/O passes/O away/O suddenly/O ./O 
The/O police/O conduct/O a/O post/O mortem/O and/O as/O a/O result/O find/O out/O that/O Mrs/O D/O sa/O was/O poisoned/O ./O 
Raj/PERSON became/O the/O prime/O suspect/O and/O is/O subsequently/O taken/O for/O questioning/O and/O is/O arrested/O and/O held/O in/O a/O cell/O ./O 
In/O the/O trial/O that/O he/O faces/O however/O Ramnath/PERSON reveals/O the/O truth/O and/O thus/O Raj/PERSON is/O saved/O ./O 
It/O takes/O place/O in/O Paris/LOCATION and/O features/O Eddie/PERSON Vuibert/PERSON an/O unemployed/O man/O in/O financial/O difficulty/O ./O 
A/O rich/O Jewish/O cloth/O manufacturer/O takes/O Eddie/PERSON into/O his/O corporation/O out/O of/O pity/O because/O he/O mistakenly/O believes/O him/O to/O be/O Jewish/O as/O well/O ./O 
Eddie/PERSON rapidly/O integrates/O in/O the/O parisian/O Jewish/O community/O and/O rises/O as/O a/O sales/O manager/O ./O 
He/O continues/O his/O masquerade/O of/O pretending/O to/O be/O Ashkenazi/O Jew/O in/O order/O to/O woo/O his/O boss/O s/O daughter/O ./O 
It/O was/O followed/O by/O a/O sequel/O La/O Verite/O si/O je/O mens/O 2/O and/O a/O third/O movie/O La/O Verite/O si/O je/O mens/O 3/O The/O film/O stars/O Remy/PERSON Girard/PERSON and/O Pauline/PERSON Lapointe/PERSON as/O Leo/PERSON and/O Ginette/PERSON Lesperance/PERSON a/O married/O couple/O who/O after/O facing/O one/O too/O many/O Montreal/LOCATION winters/O move/O their/O family/O to/O Fort/LOCATION Lauderdale/LOCATION where/O they/O buy/O a/O motel/O catering/O to/O snowbirds/O ./O 
However/O their/O new/O business/O runs/O afoul/O of/O Big/O Daddy/O an/O established/O motel/O operator/O and/O local/O crime/O boss/O who/O makes/O it/O his/O mission/O to/O drive/O the/O Lesperances/O out/O of/O business/O ./O 
The/O Lesperances/O may/O however/O have/O an/O ally/O in/O Jay/PERSON Lamori/PERSON a/O local/O businessman/O of/O uncertain/O motives/O who/O may/O or/O may/O not/O be/O what/O he/O seems/O ./O 
The/O story/O covers/O the/O lives/O of/O snowboarding/O buddies/O Rick/PERSON Luke/PERSON Anthony/PERSON and/O Pig/PERSON Pen/PERSON who/O are/O living/O large/O in/O their/O beloved/O hometown/O of/O Bull/LOCATION Mountain/LOCATION in/O Alaska/LOCATION ./O 
Partying/O hard/O looking/O for/O girls/O and/O doing/O just/O about/O anything/O to/O have/O a/O good/O time/O is/O what/O life/O on/O Bull/LOCATION Mountain/LOCATION is/O all/O about/O but/O that/O all/O looks/O to/O have/O a/O quick/O end/O when/O town/O founder/O Papa/PERSON Muntz/PERSON dies/O and/O his/O son/O Ted/PERSON decides/O to/O sell/O the/O mountain/O to/O slick/O Colorado/LOCATION businessman/O John/PERSON Majors/PERSON ./O 
Nobody/O supports/O his/O plans/O to/O turn/O the/O mountain/O into/O an/O espresso/O and/O tofu/O ski/O resort/O and/O it/O s/O up/O to/O Luke/PERSON Pig/PERSON Pen/PERSON Anthony/PERSON Jenny/PERSON Rick/PERSON and/O the/O others/O to/O keep/O Bull/ORGANIZATION Mountain/ORGANIZATION yuppie/O free/O ./O 
Once/O they/O realize/O John/PERSON s/O purchase/O will/O change/O the/O town/O drastically/O they/O enlist/O the/O aid/O of/O Major/O s/O beautiful/O rebellious/O daughters/O Inga/PERSON and/O Anna/PERSON to/O sabotage/O the/O purchase/O ./O 
The/O film/O also/O features/O a/O cameo/O by/O snowboarding/O professional/O Todd/PERSON Richards/PERSON as/O Barry/PERSON the/O Doctor/O ./O 
Wilbur/PERSON is/O a/O middle/O class/O furniture/O store/O employee/O ./O 
His/O wife/O Jessie/PERSON reads/O a/O book/O about/O how/O women/O can/O make/O their/O men/O more/O successful/O and/O decides/O to/O remake/O her/O husband/O to/O give/O him/O a/O new/O image/O ./O 
Now/O dressed/O for/O success/O by/O his/O wife/O Wilbur/PERSON reports/O for/O work/O in/O fancy/O clothes/O ./O 
Thinking/O he/O is/O dressed/O for/O a/O funeral/O his/O boss/O sends/O Wilbur/PERSON home/O for/O the/O day/O ./O 
When/O Wilbur/PERSON is/O wandering/O perplexed/O in/O a/O nearby/O park/O he/O is/O mistaken/O for/O the/O Park/O Commissioner/O ./O 
Seeing/O it/O as/O an/O opportunity/O McIntosh/O a/O crooked/O politician/O who/O wishes/O to/O land/O a/O lucrative/O deal/O with/O the/O city/O to/O sell/O them/O new/O playground/O equipment/O has/O the/O mayor/O appoint/O Wilbur/PERSON as/O Playground/O Commissioner/O ./O 
Later/O when/O Wilbur/PERSON is/O about/O to/O denounce/O McIntosh/PERSON as/O a/O crook/O McIntosh/PERSON has/O his/O wife/O ply/O Wilbur/PERSON with/O champagne/O ./O 
While/O Wilbur/PERSON is/O tipsy/O Jessie/PERSON overhears/O a/O flirtateous/O and/O damning/O conversation/O between/O the/O two/O ./O 
Wilbur/PERSON wakes/O up/O with/O a/O hangover/O no/O pants/O and/O learns/O that/O while/O intoxicated/O he/O brought/O disgrace/O to/O himself/O the/O town/O and/O his/O wife/O ./O 
Wilbur/PERSON eventually/O exposes/O the/O political/O corruption/O and/O when/O his/O wife/O finally/O agrees/O to/O let/O him/O leave/O politics/O everything/O turns/O out/O okay/O ./O 
When/O the/O circus/O comes/O to/O a/O small/O town/O resident/O Joanna/PERSON Ryan/PERSON becomes/O pregnant/O by/O horse/O trick/O rider/O Pierre/PERSON Radier/PERSON ./O 
He/O offers/O to/O marry/O her/O but/O she/O decides/O they/O are/O not/O suited/O for/O each/O other/O ./O 
Instead/O she/O marries/O steady/O local/O Elmer/PERSON Croy/PERSON ./O 
Pierre/PERSON gives/O her/O all/O his/O money/O for/O their/O child/O ./O 
Pierre/PERSON hates/O the/O circus/O life/O so/O when/O his/O friend/O Henry/PERSON Mueller/PERSON approaches/O him/O to/O become/O his/O partner/O in/O a/O bicycle/O shop/O he/O jumps/O at/O the/O chance/O despite/O the/O disapproval/O of/O his/O alcoholic/O mother/O Madame/PERSON Azais/PERSON ./O 
To/O raise/O his/O share/O of/O the/O money/O needed/O to/O start/O the/O venture/O he/O turns/O to/O wealthy/O young/O widow/O Leah/PERSON Ernst/PERSON who/O is/O attracted/O to/O him/O ./O 
The/O shop/O is/O a/O success/O but/O Pierre/PERSON s/O ambitions/O are/O only/O whetted/O ./O 
He/O persuades/O his/O partner/O to/O branch/O out/O into/O newfangled/O automobiles/O ./O 
They/O spend/O several/O years/O building/O a/O new/O car/O ./O 
By/O a/O stroke/O of/O luck/O the/O automobile/O of/O Homer/LOCATION Flint/LOCATION the/O richest/O man/O in/O the/O state/O breaks/O down/O near/O their/O shop/O ./O 
He/O is/O interested/O in/O mass/O producing/O their/O car/O ./O 
Pierre/PERSON becomes/O a/O hardworking/O business/O partner/O of/O Flint/LOCATION s/O and/O marries/O Flint/LOCATION s/O daughter/O Hazel/PERSON ./O 
However/O she/O becomes/O dissatisfied/O with/O his/O preference/O for/O late/O nights/O at/O work/O over/O her/O company/O ./O 
When/O the/O unhappy/O couple/O go/O golfing/O Pierre/PERSON now/O calling/O himself/O Paul/PERSON Rader/PERSON discovers/O that/O the/O young/O boy/O who/O wants/O to/O caddy/O for/O him/O is/O his/O son/O Pierre/PERSON Croy/PERSON ./O 
He/O secretly/O meets/O Joanna/PERSON and/O offers/O to/O adopt/O their/O child/O but/O she/O refuses/O to/O give/O him/O up/O he/O has/O to/O content/O himself/O with/O visits/O and/O gifts/O ./O 
He/O does/O however/O persuade/O her/O to/O let/O him/O send/O their/O son/O to/O a/O good/O school/O when/O he/O is/O older/O ./O 
On/O a/O business/O trip/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION he/O starts/O an/O affair/O with/O Lady/O Claire/PERSON Benston/PERSON ./O 
Yearning/O to/O be/O totally/O independent/O Paul/PERSON gives/O his/O entire/O fortune/O to/O a/O shady/O stock/O speculator/O to/O manipulate/O Rader/PERSON and/O Flint/LOCATION company/O stock/O ./O 
Flint/LOCATION finds/O out/O and/O warns/O him/O that/O he/O is/O getting/O into/O trouble/O to/O no/O avail/O ./O 
It/O all/O comes/O crashing/O down/O ./O 
The/O stock/O speculator/O turns/O out/O to/O be/O a/O swindler/O and/O absconds/O with/O all/O of/O Paul/PERSON s/O money/O and/O 7/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O of/O Lady/PERSON Benston/PERSON s/O Paul/PERSON is/O also/O devastated/O to/O learn/O that/O his/O son/O has/O been/O killed/O in/O a/O car/O crash/O the/O car/O being/O a/O birthday/O gift/O from/O him/O ./O 
When/O he/O brings/O the/O body/O to/O the/O grieving/O mother/O she/O refuses/O to/O shake/O his/O hand/O ./O 
Finally/O Hazel/PERSON learns/O of/O Pierre/PERSON s/O parentage/O ending/O their/O marriage/O ./O 
Ruined/O and/O heartsick/O Paul/PERSON seeks/O out/O his/O mother/O ./O 
She/O comforts/O him/O telling/O him/O that/O he/O has/O finally/O learned/O what/O is/O important/O and/O that/O he/O can/O make/O a/O fresh/O start/O in/O Europe/LOCATION ./O 
He/O is/O heartened/O by/O her/O faith/O in/O him/O ./O 
Montague/PERSON L/PERSON Brewster/PERSON a/O newly/O discharged/O US/LOCATION soldier/O back/O from/O fighting/O in/O Europe/LOCATION during/O World/O War/O II/O rushes/O home/O to/O marry/O his/O sweetheart/O Peggy/PERSON Gray/PERSON ./O 
However/O he/O has/O to/O postpone/O the/O wedding/O after/O he/O learns/O of/O a/O strange/O windfall/O ./O 
His/O deceased/O uncle/O has/O left/O him/O 8/O million/O but/O he/O can/O inherit/O the/O money/O only/O if/O he/O can/O spend/O a/O million/O of/O it/O before/O his/O 3/O 0/O th/O birthday/O only/O two/O months/O away/O without/O keeping/O any/O assets/O ./O 
The/O lawyer/O explains/O that/O Brewster/PERSON s/O relative/O hoped/O it/O would/O make/O him/O so/O sick/O of/O spending/O that/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O fortune/O would/O not/O be/O wasted/O ./O 
The/O conditions/O include/O not/O telling/O anyone/O what/O he/O is/O doing/O ./O 
Brewster/PERSON reluctantly/O agrees/O ./O 
Brewster/PERSON sets/O up/O his/O own/O investment/O company/O called/O Brewster/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION and/O hires/O his/O wartime/O buddies/O Hacky/PERSON Smith/PERSON and/O Noppy/PERSON Harrison/PERSON as/O vice/O presidents/O and/O Peggy/PERSON as/O his/O private/O secretary/O ./O 
However/O despite/O his/O best/O efforts/O most/O of/O his/O schemes/O to/O lose/O money/O become/O profitable/O ./O 
Worse/O Peggy/PERSON becomes/O jealous/O of/O Brewster/PERSON spending/O a/O great/O deal/O of/O time/O with/O first/O socialite/O Barbara/PERSON Drew/PERSON then/O showgirl/O Trixie/O Summers/O even/O though/O he/O is/O only/O using/O them/O to/O help/O squander/O the/O million/O ./O 
Smith/PERSON and/O Harrison/PERSON mistakingly/O thinking/O that/O Brewster/PERSON has/O gone/O crazy/O due/O to/O his/O spending/O sprees/O begin/O to/O toward/O all/O of/O his/O spending/O schemes/O ./O 
At/O the/O same/O time/O Peggy/PERSON breaks/O up/O with/O Brewster/PERSON but/O her/O wise/O mother/O persuades/O her/O to/O go/O on/O a/O costly/O cruise/O with/O him/O and/O the/O cast/O of/O a/O failed/O play/O he/O financed/O after/O Smith/PERSON and/O Harrison/PERSON close/O it/O down/O ./O 
During/O the/O cruise/O Smith/PERSON and/O Harrison/PERSON stage/O a/O rebellion/O by/O confining/O Brewster/PERSON to/O his/O quarters/O and/O ordering/O Brewster/PERSON s/O chartared/O yacht/O turned/O around/O to/O return/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION thinking/O that/O Brewster/PERSON has/O lost/O his/O mind/O by/O financing/O this/O pointless/O cruise/O ./O 
When/O Brewster/PERSON s/O chartered/O yacht/O is/O disabled/O by/O a/O leftover/O U/O boat/O mine/O he/O escapes/O from/O his/O containment/O and/O makes/O it/O to/O the/O bridge/O to/O order/O the/O captain/O radio/O for/O help/O ./O 
Brewster/PERSON is/O ecstatic/O to/O learn/O that/O getting/O a/O tow/O from/O a/O passing/O Brazilian/O freighter/O to/O a/O nearby/O Florida/LOCATION port/O will/O cost/O him/O a/O huge/O salvage/O fee/O of/O over/O a/O few/O hundred/O thousand/O dollars/O ./O 
He/O learns/O that/O this/O is/O all/O of/O the/O last/O amount/O of/O money/O to/O spend/O ./O 
In/O the/O final/O scene/O set/O a/O few/O days/O later/O as/O the/O deadline/O approaches/O Brewster/PERSON thinks/O he/O has/O met/O his/O goal/O only/O to/O have/O his/O friends/O present/O him/O with/O 4/O 0/O 0/O 1/O 2/O that/O they/O have/O recovered/O from/O his/O failed/O ventures/O ./O 
Luckily/O as/O the/O clock/O to/O the/O deadline/O strikes/O 1/O 2/O noon/O he/O is/O able/O to/O get/O rid/O of/O the/O money/O by/O paying/O the/O executor/O s/O fee/O an/O old/O 1/O 0/O debt/O and/O the/O last/O 2/O for/O a/O cab/O fare/O just/O before/O time/O runs/O out/O ./O 
Having/O secured/O his/O inhertence/O of/O 7/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O Brewster/PERSON then/O takes/O Peggy/PERSON out/O saying/O that/O they/O have/O to/O go/O downtown/O to/O the/O nearist/O justice/O of/O the/O peace/O to/O get/O married/O right/O away/O ./O 
Mr./O Zygmunt/PERSON Sawicki/PERSON is/O a/O bank/O employee/O who/O finds/O a/O camel/O in/O his/O yard/O one/O day/O ./O 
He/O decides/O to/O take/O charge/O of/O it/O and/O he/O and/O his/O wife/O Marysia/LOCATION take/O care/O of/O it/O ./O 
However/O problems/O arise/O for/O both/O his/O fellow/O town/O dwellers/O and/O the/O local/O authorities/O ./O 
Down/O at/O the/O local/O labour/O exchange/O everyone/O is/O moaning/O about/O the/O lack/O of/O decent/O jobs/O unaware/O that/O nearby/O Bert/PERSON Handy/PERSON and/O his/O secretary/O Miss/O Cooling/O are/O attempting/O to/O fill/O vacancies/O at/O a/O new/O enterprise/O called/O Helping/O Hands/O ./O 
When/O word/O gets/O round/O people/O are/O quick/O to/O visit/O the/O agency/O notably/O Sam/PERSON Twist/PERSON Francis/PERSON Courtenay/PERSON Delia/PERSON King/PERSON Gabriel/PERSON Dimple/PERSON Lily/PERSON Duveen/PERSON Mike/PERSON Weston/PERSON and/O Montgomery/O Infield/O Hopping/O ./O 
Bert/PERSON decides/O to/O hire/O them/O all/O and/O at/O first/O business/O is/O slow/O ./O 
The/O only/O customer/O is/O a/O man/O who/O speaks/O gobbledygook/O but/O since/O Francis/PERSON isn/O t/O present/O nobody/O can/O understand/O him/O and/O he/O goes/O on/O his/O way/O ./O 
Within/O a/O few/O days/O business/O picks/O up/O and/O Delia/PERSON has/O an/O assignment/O to/O try/O on/O a/O complete/O women/O s/O wardrobe/O for/O Mr/O Delling/PERSON a/O gentleman/O who/O is/O planning/O a/O surprise/O for/O his/O wife/O ./O 
However/O things/O get/O complicated/O when/O the/O mans/O wife/O arrives/O home/O unexpectedly/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O Sam/PERSON Twist/PERSON is/O sent/O to/O a/O baby/O sitting/O job/O only/O to/O find/O that/O there/O isn/O t/O a/O baby/O to/O be/O sitted/O instead/O there/O is/O Mrs/O Panting/O a/O woman/O who/O needs/O to/O make/O her/O husband/O jealous/O ./O 
The/O following/O day/O Francis/PERSON is/O assigned/O to/O take/O a/O pet/O for/O a/O walk/O but/O when/O he/O gets/O to/O the/O owner/O s/O house/O he/O finds/O out/O it/O s/O a/O chimpanzee/O ./O 
He/O takes/O the/O chimp/O for/O a/O walk/O and/O soon/O discovers/O that/O people/O who/O work/O in/O the/O transport/O industry/O have/O an/O aversion/O to/O apes/O ./O 
They/O eventually/O end/O up/O at/O a/O chimps/O tea/O party/O enjoying/O a/O nice/O afternoon/O tea/O ./O 
Next/O up/O is/O Lily/PERSON Duveen/PERSON who/O has/O been/O employed/O at/O a/O wine/O tasting/O evening/O to/O collect/O invitation/O cards/O from/O the/O attendees/O ./O 
After/O she/O has/O performed/O this/O task/O she/O samples/O some/O of/O the/O wines/O and/O makes/O a/O bit/O of/O a/O spectacle/O of/O herself/O ./O 
Later/O a/O man/O from/O Amalgamated/O Scrap/O Iron/O arrives/O in/O the/O Helping/O Hands/O office/O ./O 
He/O s/O obviously/O busy/O as/O he/O requests/O that/O someone/O take/O his/O place/O in/O the/O queue/O at/O the/O hospital/O outpatients/O department/O ./O 
Bert/PERSON says/O he/O will/O get/O someone/O on/O the/O case/O but/O the/O chap/O insists/O that/O the/O top/O man/O does/O the/O job/O himself/O so/O Bert/PERSON ends/O up/O queuing/O at/O the/O hospital/O where/O he/O is/O mistaken/O for/O an/O eminent/O diagnostician/O ./O 
The/O next/O job/O that/O Francis/PERSON undertakes/O is/O in/O the/O field/O of/O photography/O as/O a/O model/O ./O 
Obviously/O very/O chuffed/O that/O he/O has/O been/O chosen/O he/O is/O crestfallen/O when/O he/O discovers/O that/O the/O job/O is/O an/O advertisement/O for/O a/O bee/O keepers/O helmet/O ./O 
His/O next/O job/O is/O between/O a/O bickering/O couple/O ./O 
The/O husband/O can/O t/O understand/O his/O wife/O who/O continually/O berates/O him/O in/O her/O native/O German/O ./O 
Thanks/O to/O Francis/PERSON getting/O a/O bit/O emotionally/O involved/O the/O wife/O starts/O speaking/O English/O and/O the/O couple/O make/O up/O ./O 
Lefty/O Vincent/PERSON a/O boxing/O friend/O of/O Berts/O pops/O into/O the/O office/O ./O 
He/O requires/O four/O helpers/O to/O act/O as/O seconds/O for/O his/O fighter/O Dynamite/O Dan/PERSON ./O 
When/O they/O get/O to/O the/O venue/O Dan/PERSON is/O terrified/O by/O his/O opponent/O Mickey/PERSON McGee/PERSON so/O pretends/O that/O he/O has/O sprained/O his/O finger/O ./O 
The/O fight/O is/O off/O until/O Gabriel/PERSON takes/O on/O McGee/PERSON instead/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON is/O excited/O over/O his/O next/O job/O ./O 
He/O thinks/O he/O s/O on/O a/O top/O secret/O spying/O mission/O but/O due/O to/O a/O mix/O up/O all/O that/O is/O required/O of/O him/O is/O to/O make/O up/O a/O game/O of/O bridge/O ./O 
When/O Sam/PERSON gets/O back/O he/O learns/O that/O the/O whole/O of/O Helping/O Hands/O have/O been/O engaged/O to/O demonstrate/O exhibits/O at/O the/O Ideal/ORGANIZATION House/ORGANIZATION exhibition/O ./O 
Needless/O to/O say/O all/O of/O the/O demonstrations/O end/O in/O calamity/O ./O 
Sam/PERSON s/O next/O job/O is/O at/O an/O exclusive/O men/O s/O club/O where/O no/O matter/O how/O hard/O he/O tries/O he/O can/O t/O keep/O silent/O which/O is/O a/O strict/O rule/O of/O the/O establishment/O ./O 
Miss/O Cooling/O decides/O on/O a/O new/O filing/O system/O for/O a/O more/O streamlined/O operation/O and/O job/O cards/O are/O put/O in/O cubby/O holes/O for/O each/O of/O the/O workers/O ./O 
Disaster/O strikes/O when/O the/O cleaner/O knocks/O the/O box/O down/O and/O puts/O the/O cards/O back/O all/O mixed/O up/O ./O 
Everyone/O gets/O someone/O else/O s/O assignment/O with/O misunderstandings/O all/O round/O ./O 
Finally/O the/O gobbledygook/O man/O turns/O up/O again/O and/O this/O time/O Francis/PERSON is/O there/O to/O translate/O ./O 
He/O is/O their/O landlord/O and/O has/O been/O trying/O to/O inform/O Bert/PERSON that/O he/O will/O have/O to/O vacate/O the/O premises/O because/O he/O s/O had/O a/O better/O offer/O ./O 
Due/O to/O a/O show/O of/O unity/O by/O all/O the/O staff/O the/O landlord/O agrees/O that/O they/O can/O stay/O on/O the/O provision/O that/O they/O do/O something/O for/O him/O ./O 
His/O main/O interest/O is/O property/O development/O and/O he/O needs/O a/O house/O cleared/O and/O cleaned/O ./O 
Unfortunately/O the/O team/O end/O up/O demolishing/O the/O house/O but/O thankfully/O it/O turns/O out/O that/O it/O needed/O demolishing/O for/O a/O block/O of/O flats/O anyway/O so/O all/O ends/O well/O ./O 
The/O film/O follows/O the/O trials/O of/O tenant/O farmer/O Ramon/PERSON Garcia/PERSON and/O his/O wife/O Soledad/PERSON when/O drought/O forces/O them/O off/O their/O land/O in/O the/O Mexican/O state/O of/O Zacatecas/LOCATION ./O 
They/O make/O their/O way/O to/O Mexico/LOCATION City/LOCATION where/O they/O find/O city/O life/O difficult/O ./O 
Ramon/PERSON can/O not/O find/O steady/O work/O ./O 
They/O build/O a/O home/O in/O a/O squatters/O settlement/O but/O then/O their/O house/O is/O bulldozed/O by/O a/O developer/O ./O 
Soledad/PERSON finds/O work/O as/O a/O live/O in/O maid/O and/O her/O husband/O can/O see/O her/O for/O only/O a/O few/O moments/O each/O evening/O ./O 
Ramon/PERSON destitute/O and/O despondent/O wanders/O into/O a/O theater/O during/O a/O live/O radio/O broadcast/O of/O an/O audience/O participation/O talent/O show/O ./O 
Ramon/PERSON volunteers/O for/O the/O show/O and/O although/O the/O host/O makes/O fun/O of/O him/O as/O a/O hayseed/O he/O wows/O the/O audience/O with/O a/O stirring/O version/O of/O the/O classic/O Mexico/O Lindo/O ./O 
The/O audience/O reaction/O causes/O the/O station/O manager/O to/O hire/O Garcia/PERSON as/O a/O featured/O performer/O as/O a/O change/O of/O pace/O from/O more/O trendy/O musical/O genres/O ./O 
Garcia/PERSON gains/O a/O wide/O radio/O following/O by/O singing/O traditional/O songs/O praising/O the/O virtues/O of/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O 
Now/O highly/O paid/O and/O famous/O Garcia/PERSON rents/O a/O luxurious/O apartment/O but/O his/O wife/O Soledad/PERSON fears/O that/O they/O do/O not/O belong/O in/O their/O new/O and/O rich/O surroundings/O ./O 
Soledad/PERSON s/O fears/O turn/O out/O to/O be/O prescient/O as/O her/O husband/O soon/O falls/O into/O the/O clutches/O of/O Mirta/LOCATION a/O blonde/O with/O a/O heavy/O American/O accent/O ./O 
In/O the/O end/O however/O Ramon/PERSON realizes/O that/O he/O belongs/O with/O his/O loyal/O wife/O ./O 
Wang/PERSON Xiaojian/PERSON is/O a/O down/O and/O out/O slacker/O in/O a/O small/O town/O in/O China/LOCATION s/O industrial/O Shaanxi/LOCATION province/LOCATION ./O 
His/O father/O a/O factory/O worker/O has/O fallen/O ill/O and/O prospects/O for/O both/O Xiaojian/PERSON and/O his/O family/O look/O dim/O ./O 
Stuck/O working/O in/O his/O family/O s/O tailoring/O and/O laundry/O shop/O one/O day/O Xiaojian/PERSON comes/O across/O the/O freshly/O laundered/O uniform/O of/O a/O police/O officer/O ./O 
Attempting/O to/O deliver/O it/O he/O discovers/O that/O the/O police/O office/O who/O the/O uniform/O was/O intended/O had/O been/O injured/O and/O would/O not/O be/O back/O on/O the/O job/O for/O a/O few/O weeks/O ./O 
Wandering/O home/O Xiaojian/PERSON decides/O to/O try/O the/O uniform/O on/O ./O 
Suddenly/O Xiaojian/PERSON s/O life/O begins/O to/O turn/O around/O as/O people/O mistake/O him/O for/O a/O police/O officer/O a/O mistake/O he/O quickly/O capitalizes/O on/O ./O 
Using/O the/O uniform/O Xiaojian/PERSON begins/O stopping/O motorists/O and/O bus/O drivers/O in/O order/O to/O shake/O them/O down/O for/O bribes/O in/O order/O to/O pay/O for/O his/O father/O s/O medical/O expenses/O ./O 
Less/O noble/O he/O uses/O the/O uniform/O to/O begin/O wooing/O a/O pretty/O clerk/O Zheng/PERSON Shasha/PERSON ./O 
As/O they/O begin/O seeing/O each/O other/O more/O regularly/O however/O it/O becomes/O clear/O that/O Xiaojian/PERSON is/O not/O the/O only/O one/O living/O a/O double/O life/O ./O 
Stratis/PERSON after/O many/O years/O of/O laborious/O work/O publishes/O his/O treatise/O on/O Aspasia/PERSON s/O role/O in/O the/O Peloponnesian/O Wars/O ./O 
A/O team/O of/O American/O film/O producers/O approaches/O him/O to/O get/O the/O movie/O rights/O planning/O to/O use/O his/O scientific/O work/O for/O a/O historical/O parody/O ./O 
At/O first/O he/O rejects/O their/O offer/O but/O finally/O life/O s/O demands/O and/O his/O debts/O to/O his/O relatives/O compel/O him/O to/O accept/O ./O 
At/O the/O same/O time/O he/O falls/O in/O love/O with/O his/O cinematic/O heroine/O ./O 
In/O the/O end/O after/O the/O completion/O of/O the/O shooting/O of/O the/O film/O his/O luck/O changes/O and/O he/O is/O able/O to/O return/O to/O his/O old/O ways/O ./O 
In/O the/O wake/O of/O a/O banking/O crisis/O four/O middle/O class/O friends/O throw/O a/O white/O glove/O hold/O up/O only/O to/O find/O out/O that/O their/O bank/O has/O already/O gone/O bankrupt/O ./O 
John/PERSON Smith/PERSON fought/O for/O his/O country/O in/O World/O War/O I/O But/O during/O the/O depression/O of/O the/O 1/O 9/O 3/O 0/O s/O he/O found/O it/O hard/O to/O find/O work/O ./O 
Finally/O the/O bailiffs/O appear/O and/O take/O everything/O of/O value/O ./O 
His/O loyal/O wife/O Mary/PERSON Smith/PERSON tells/O John/PERSON about/O a/O charity/O for/O ex/O servicemen/O ./O 
John/PERSON appeals/O to/O the/O charity/O and/O they/O help/O him/O They/O give/O him/O a/O loan/O to/O get/O him/O back/O on/O his/O feet/O and/O they/O train/O him/O in/O skills/O that/O are/O more/O useful/O than/O the/O ones/O he/O had/O before/O ./O 
A/O large/O part/O of/O the/O short/O film/O is/O taken/O up/O with/O a/O long/O speech/O by/O Major/ORGANIZATION Lloyd/ORGANIZATION from/O the/O charity/O as/O the/O camera/O shows/O us/O around/O ./O 
There/O are/O examples/O of/O ex/O servicemen/O doing/O wickerwork/O and/O other/O small/O handicrafts/O ./O 
Martin/PERSON Raikes/PERSON is/O a/O bank/O investigator/O who/O is/O sent/O to/O Monaco/LOCATION to/O check/O up/O on/O the/O shady/O dealings/O of/O a/O movie/O production/O ./O 
After/O the/O business/O trip/O he/O ll/O then/O fly/O over/O to/O London/LOCATION to/O visit/O his/O daughter/O ./O 
When/O Martin/PERSON arrives/O in/O Monaco/LOCATION he/O is/O met/O by/O the/O film/O company/O s/O CFO/O Lela/PERSON Forin/PERSON and/O washed/O up/O action/O star/O Jake/PERSON Mellows/PERSON ./O 
Something/O is/O rotten/O with/O the/O production/O though/O and/O Martin/PERSON senses/O it/O ./O 
Unfortunately/O he/O sticks/O his/O nose/O in/O a/O little/O too/O deep/O for/O the/O corrupt/O bankrollers/O tastes/O and/O is/O soon/O deemed/O a/O threat/O to/O them/O ./O 
Martin/PERSON is/O first/O offered/O a/O mega/O bribe/O but/O he/O rejects/O it/O ./O 
As/O it/O turns/O out/O the/O bankrollers/O are/O Russian/O mafia/O led/O by/O Oleg/PERSON Butraskaya/PERSON ./O 
Suddenly/O Martin/PERSON finds/O himself/O framed/O for/O an/O assassination/O attempt/O and/O the/O hostile/O authorities/O on/O the/O payroll/O of/O the/O mob/O want/O to/O kill/O him/O ./O 
The/O American/O authorities/O are/O also/O hot/O on/O his/O trail/O investigating/O him/O for/O money/O laundering/O among/O other/O false/O charges/O ./O 
As/O Martin/PERSON sifts/O through/O the/O mystery/O he/O reveals/O the/O nefarious/O nature/O of/O Oleg/PERSON s/O rackets/O which/O include/O illegal/O pornography/O and/O money/O laundering/O ./O 
Not/O knowing/O whom/O to/O trust/O he/O turns/O to/O Lela/PERSON ./O 
Soon/O she/O too/O is/O marked/O for/O death/O and/O the/O two/O go/O on/O the/O run/O before/O meeting/O up/O with/O Jake/PERSON who/O joins/O the/O group/O ./O 
They/O put/O their/O minds/O together/O desperate/O to/O find/O a/O way/O to/O clear/O their/O names/O and/O survive/O ./O 
A/O family/O with/O financial/O difficulties/O is/O a/O brilliant/O idea/O to/O make/O the/O daughter/O Lindinha/PERSON impregnate/O the/O famous/O singer/O Ivan/PERSON Claudio/PERSON the/O king/O of/O Xique/LOCATION ./O 
They/O just/O did/O not/O have/O a/O jealous/O Jennifer/PERSON wife/O of/O Ivan/PERSON who/O will/O not/O let/O this/O story/O cheap/O ./O 
In/O 1/O 9/O 8/O 1/O San/LOCATION Francisco/LOCATION Chris/PERSON Gardner/PERSON invests/O his/O family/O s/O savings/O in/O portable/O bone/O density/O scanners/O which/O he/O tries/O to/O demonstrate/O and/O sell/O to/O doctors/O ./O 
The/O investment/O proves/O to/O be/O a/O white/O elephant/O which/O financially/O breaks/O the/O family/O and/O as/O a/O result/O his/O wife/O Linda/PERSON leaves/O him/O and/O moves/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION ./O 
Their/O son/O Christopher/PERSON remains/O with/O his/O father/O ./O 
While/O downtown/O trying/O to/O sell/O one/O of/O his/O scanners/O Chris/PERSON meets/O Jay/PERSON Twistle/PERSON a/O manager/O for/O Dean/PERSON Witter/PERSON and/O impresses/O him/O by/O solving/O a/O Rubik/O s/O Cube/O during/O a/O short/O cab/O ride/O ./O 
Chris/PERSON does/O not/O have/O enough/O money/O for/O the/O cab/O fare/O and/O flees/O into/O a/O subway/O station/O where/O he/O barely/O escapes/O the/O cab/O driver/O but/O loses/O one/O of/O his/O bone/O scanners/O in/O the/O process/O ./O 
This/O new/O relationship/O with/O Twistle/PERSON earns/O him/O the/O chance/O to/O become/O an/O intern/O stockbroker/O ./O 
Despite/O arriving/O there/O unkempt/O and/O shabbily/O dressed/O due/O to/O being/O arrested/O the/O previous/O day/O for/O unpaid/O parking/O tickets/O and/O Chris/PERSON didn/O t/O have/O enough/O time/O to/O make/O the/O appointment/O on/O time/O Chris/PERSON is/O offered/O the/O internship/O ./O 
Chris/PERSON is/O further/O set/O back/O when/O his/O bank/O account/O is/O garnished/O by/O the/O IRS/ORGANIZATION for/O unpaid/O income/O taxes/O and/O he/O and/O his/O young/O son/O are/O evicted/O ./O 
As/O a/O result/O they/O are/O homeless/O and/O are/O forced/O at/O one/O point/O to/O stay/O in/O a/O bathroom/O at/O a/O subway/O station/O ./O 
Motivation/O drives/O him/O to/O find/O the/O Glide/ORGANIZATION Memorial/ORGANIZATION United/ORGANIZATION Methodist/ORGANIZATION Church/ORGANIZATION which/O has/O a/O homeless/O shelter/O primarily/O for/O single/O mothers/O and/O their/O children/O ./O 
The/O church/O s/O owner/O does/O not/O let/O him/O stay/O due/O to/O the/O fact/O that/O it/O is/O for/O women/O and/O children/O although/O she/O tells/O him/O about/O a/O local/O church/O that/O also/O provides/O shelter/O but/O has/O very/O limited/O space/O ./O 
Due/O to/O demand/O for/O the/O limited/O rooms/O Chris/PERSON must/O frantically/O race/O from/O his/O internship/O work/O early/O each/O afternoon/O in/O order/O to/O land/O a/O place/O in/O line/O ./O 
Chris/PERSON finds/O the/O bone/O scanner/O that/O he/O lost/O in/O the/O subway/O station/O from/O a/O demented/O man/O who/O believes/O it/O to/O be/O a/O time/O machine/O and/O it/O is/O now/O damaged/O but/O Chris/PERSON finally/O repairs/O it/O ./O 
Disadvantaged/O by/O his/O limited/O work/O hours/O and/O knowing/O that/O maximizing/O his/O client/O contacts/O and/O profits/O is/O the/O only/O way/O to/O earn/O the/O one/O paid/O position/O that/O he/O and/O his/O 1/O 9/O competitors/O are/O fighting/O for/O Chris/PERSON develops/O a/O number/O of/O ways/O to/O make/O phone/O sales/O calls/O more/O efficiently/O ./O 
He/O also/O reaches/O out/O to/O potential/O high/O value/O customers/O defying/O protocol/O ./O 
One/O sympathetic/O prospect/O takes/O him/O and/O his/O son/O to/O a/O San/ORGANIZATION Francisco/ORGANIZATION 4/O 9/O ers/O game/O ./O 
Regardless/O of/O his/O challenges/O Chris/PERSON never/O reveals/O his/O lowly/O circumstances/O to/O his/O co/O workers/O even/O going/O so/O far/O as/O to/O lend/O one/O of/O his/O bosses/O five/O dollars/O for/O a/O cab/O a/O sum/O he/O can/O t/O afford/O ./O 
Concluding/O his/O internship/O Chris/PERSON is/O called/O into/O a/O meeting/O with/O his/O managers/O ./O 
His/O work/O has/O paid/O off/O and/O he/O is/O offered/O the/O position/O ./O 
Fighting/O back/O tears/O he/O rushes/O to/O his/O son/O s/O daycare/O hugging/O him/O ./O 
They/O walk/O down/O the/O street/O joking/O with/O each/O other/O and/O are/O passed/O by/O a/O man/O in/O a/O business/O suit/O ./O 
The/O epilogue/O reveals/O that/O Chris/PERSON went/O on/O to/O form/O his/O own/O multi/O million/O dollar/O brokerage/O firm/O ./O 
The/O story/O tells/O about/O former/O football/O hooligan/O Ray/PERSON Knight/PERSON a/O security/O guard/O at/O a/O financial/O trading/O company/O in/O Canary/ORGANIZATION Wharf/ORGANIZATION the/O symbol/O of/O corporate/O wealth/O which/O looms/O high/O over/O the/O impoverished/O communities/O below/O ./O 
Newfound/O social/O responsibilities/O are/O trampled/O underfoot/O when/O Ray/PERSON s/O racist/O past/O is/O revived/O amid/O tensions/O between/O Whites/O and/O Asians/O jostling/O for/O position/O on/O the/O council/O housing/O list/O ./O 
Among/O those/O who/O are/O wanting/O to/O be/O rehoused/O in/O a/O new/O development/O is/O Ray/PERSON s/O alcoholic/O ex/O wife/O Sadie/PERSON and/O his/O teenage/O daughter/O Nikki/PERSON ./O 
The/O film/O begins/O following/O the/O British/O victory/O of/O the/O First/O Opium/O War/O and/O the/O seizure/O of/O Hong/LOCATION Kong/LOCATION ./O 
Although/O the/O island/O is/O largely/O uninhabited/O and/O the/O terrain/O unfriendly/O it/O has/O a/O large/O port/O that/O both/O the/O British/O government/O and/O various/O trading/O companies/O believe/O will/O be/O useful/O for/O the/O import/O of/O merchandise/O to/O be/O traded/O on/O mainland/O China/LOCATION a/O highly/O lucrative/O market/O ./O 
Although/O the/O film/O features/O many/O characters/O it/O is/O arguably/O Dirk/PERSON Struan/PERSON and/O Tyler/PERSON Brock/PERSON former/O shipmates/O and/O the/O owners/O of/O two/O massive/O trading/O companies/O who/O are/O the/O main/O focal/O points/O of/O the/O story/O ./O 
Their/O rocky/O and/O often/O abusive/O relationship/O as/O seamen/O initiated/O an/O intense/O amount/O of/O competitive/O tension/O ./O 
Throughout/O both/O men/O seek/O to/O destroy/O each/O other/O in/O matters/O of/O business/O and/O personal/O affairs/O ./O 
Struan/PERSON is/O referred/O to/O as/O Tai/PERSON Pan/PERSON indicating/O his/O position/O as/O head/O of/O the/O largest/O and/O most/O profitable/O of/O all/O the/O trading/O companies/O operating/O in/O Asia/LOCATION ./O 
Brock/PERSON owner/O of/O the/O second/O largest/O of/O the/O trading/O companies/O constantly/O vies/O to/O destroy/O Struan/PERSON s/O company/O and/O reputation/O in/O an/O attempt/O to/O both/O exact/O revenge/O on/O Struan/PERSON and/O become/O the/O new/O Tai/PERSON Pan/PERSON of/O Chinese/O trade/O ./O 
While/O the/O film/O follows/O a/O similar/O structure/O as/O the/O novel/O one/O major/O and/O notable/O event/O is/O left/O out/O ./O 
Struan/PERSON s/O meeting/O with/O Jin/PERSON Qua/PERSON early/O in/O the/O film/O to/O obtain/O the/O forty/O lac/O dollars/O of/O silver/O to/O pay/O Brock/PERSON omits/O Jin/PERSON Qua/PERSON s/O stipulation/O that/O four/O special/O coins/O be/O broken/O in/O half/O with/O Struan/PERSON keeping/O four/O halves/O and/O the/O other/O four/O being/O distributed/O by/O Jin/PERSON Qua/PERSON ./O 
When/O a/O half/O coin/O is/O presented/O to/O Struan/PERSON that/O matches/O his/O own/O half/O he/O is/O obligated/O to/O do/O a/O favor/O to/O the/O bearer/O ./O 
The/O first/O favor/O is/O called/O in/O later/O in/O the/O novel/O by/O the/O pirate/O Wu/PERSON Kwok/PERSON ./O 
The/O film/O does/O not/O convey/O this/O ./O 
Arthur/PERSON Hamilton/PERSON is/O a/O middle/O aged/O man/O whose/O life/O has/O lost/O purpose/O ./O 
He/O has/O achieved/O success/O in/O his/O career/O but/O finds/O it/O unfulfilling/O ./O 
His/O love/O for/O his/O wife/O of/O many/O years/O has/O dwindled/O ./O 
His/O only/O child/O is/O married/O and/O he/O seldom/O sees/O her/O ./O 
Through/O a/O friend/O a/O man/O he/O thought/O was/O dead/O Hamilton/PERSON is/O approached/O by/O a/O secret/O organization/O known/O simply/O as/O the/O Company/O ./O 
The/O Company/O s/O business/O is/O helping/O wealthy/O people/O who/O are/O unhappy/O with/O their/O lives/O to/O disappear/O and/O create/O new/O lives/O ./O 
When/O Hamilton/PERSON agrees/O to/O talk/O to/O the/O Company/O he/O is/O spirited/O away/O to/O a/O secret/O location/O ./O 
While/O waiting/O for/O his/O interview/O he/O is/O offered/O a/O cup/O of/O tea/O and/O then/O falls/O asleep/O ./O 
When/O he/O wakes/O Hamilton/PERSON is/O interviewed/O by/O Mr/O Ruby/PERSON who/O shows/O him/O a/O film/O in/O which/O he/O appears/O to/O have/O raped/O a/O girl/O ./O 
The/O film/O made/O while/O he/O was/O unconscious/O is/O intended/O to/O persuade/O Hamilton/PERSON that/O it/O is/O now/O too/O late/O for/O him/O to/O return/O to/O his/O old/O life/O ./O 
Hamilton/PERSON feels/O compelled/O to/O accept/O the/O Company/O s/O services/O but/O fears/O that/O this/O coercive/O scheme/O foreshadows/O the/O unfortunate/O consequences/O of/O doing/O business/O with/O the/O Company/O ./O 
Hamilton/PERSON s/O death/O is/O staged/O to/O make/O it/O look/O as/O if/O he/O perished/O in/O a/O hotel/O fire/O a/O corpse/O is/O left/O at/O the/O scene/O that/O can/O be/O identified/O as/O his/O ./O 
Through/O extensive/O plastic/O surgery/O and/O mental/O and/O physical/O conditioning/O Hamilton/PERSON is/O transformed/O into/O Tony/PERSON Wilson/PERSON a/O man/O who/O looks/O and/O acts/O much/O younger/O ./O 
He/O is/O provided/O with/O a/O new/O home/O a/O new/O identity/O new/O friends/O and/O a/O devoted/O manservant/O ./O 
The/O details/O of/O his/O new/O existence/O including/O diplomas/O and/O other/O evidence/O of/O professional/O accomplishment/O that/O appear/O genuine/O suggest/O that/O there/O was/O once/O a/O real/O Tony/PERSON Wilson/PERSON but/O what/O became/O of/O him/O is/O a/O mystery/O ./O 
Hamilton/PERSON tries/O to/O adapt/O to/O his/O new/O life/O ./O 
As/O Tony/PERSON Wilson/PERSON he/O lives/O in/O a/O beach/O house/O in/O Malibu/LOCATION California/LOCATION and/O enjoys/O the/O reputation/O of/O a/O successful/O artist/O ./O 
He/O begins/O a/O relationship/O with/O a/O young/O woman/O named/O Nora/PERSON Marcus/PERSON and/O for/O a/O time/O he/O is/O happy/O ./O 
He/O then/O finds/O that/O the/O pleasures/O he/O denied/O himself/O in/O his/O first/O life/O are/O not/O exactly/O what/O he/O expected/O ./O 
At/O a/O dinner/O party/O he/O hosts/O for/O neighbors/O Wilson/PERSON drinks/O himself/O into/O a/O stupor/O and/O begins/O to/O babble/O about/O his/O former/O life/O as/O Hamilton/PERSON ./O 
It/O turns/O out/O that/O his/O neighbors/O are/O reborns/O like/O himself/O sent/O to/O keep/O an/O eye/O on/O his/O adjustment/O ./O 
Nora/PERSON is/O actually/O an/O agent/O of/O the/O Company/ORGANIZATION and/O her/O attentions/O to/O Wilson/PERSON are/O designed/O merely/O to/O ensure/O his/O cooperation/O with/O the/O Company/O s/O program/O ./O 
In/O violation/O of/O Company/O policy/O Wilson/PERSON posing/O as/O an/O old/O friend/O of/O her/O husband/O s/O visits/O his/O former/O wife/O in/O his/O new/O persona/O ./O 
He/O learns/O that/O his/O marriage/O had/O failed/O because/O he/O was/O distracted/O by/O the/O pursuit/O of/O career/O and/O material/O possessions/O the/O very/O things/O in/O life/O that/O others/O made/O him/O believe/O were/O important/O ./O 
Wilson/PERSON returns/O to/O the/O Company/ORGANIZATION and/O announces/O a/O desire/O to/O start/O again/O with/O yet/O another/O identity/O ./O 
The/O Company/O offers/O to/O accommodate/O him/O but/O asks/O if/O he/O would/O first/O provide/O the/O names/O of/O some/O past/O acquaintances/O who/O might/O like/O to/O be/O reborn/O ./O 
He/O refuses/O since/O he/O now/O knows/O of/O the/O drawbacks/O to/O being/O reborn/O and/O also/O doesn/O t/O want/O to/O delay/O the/O Company/O s/O process/O for/O giving/O him/O a/O new/O identity/O ./O 
While/O awaiting/O his/O reassignment/O Wilson/PERSON encounters/O Charlie/PERSON Evans/PERSON the/O friend/O who/O had/O originally/O recruited/O him/O into/O the/O Company/O ./O 
Evans/PERSON was/O also/O reborn/O and/O likewise/O could/O not/O make/O a/O go/O of/O his/O new/O life/O ./O 
Together/O they/O speculate/O on/O the/O reason/O for/O their/O failure/O to/O adjust/O attributing/O it/O to/O the/O fact/O that/O they/O allowed/O others/O including/O the/O Company/O to/O make/O life/O choices/O for/O them/O ./O 
This/O understanding/O comes/O too/O late/O ./O 
Wilson/PERSON Hamilton/PERSON is/O suddenly/O informed/O that/O he/O is/O to/O be/O taken/O to/O surgery/O to/O be/O given/O his/O new/O identity/O but/O as/O he/O is/O wheeled/O down/O the/O hallway/O a/O priest/O reads/O him/O the/O last/O rites/O and/O he/O realizes/O he/O is/O going/O to/O his/O death/O ./O 
He/O is/O wheeled/O into/O an/O operating/O room/O where/O he/O learns/O that/O failed/O reborns/O are/O not/O actually/O provided/O with/O new/O identities/O but/O instead/O become/O the/O cadavers/O used/O to/O fake/O new/O clients/O deaths/O ./O 
The/O original/O film/O was/O based/O on/O a/O dam/O being/O built/O across/O a/O village.The/O story/O of/O the/O film/O is/O set/O in/O a/O village/O that/O faces/O the/O threat/O of/O perishing/O if/O the/O dam/O is/O constructed/O ./O 
The/O engineer/O undertakes/O the/O project/O for/O corporate/O interests/O ./O 
The/O wife/O of/O the/O engineer/O fights/O against/O insensitive/O authorities/O that/O do/O not/O seem/O to/O be/O concerned/O with/O villagers/O woes/O ./O 
She/O is/O left/O numb/O when/O she/O learns/O that/O her/O husband/O is/O also/O a/O part/O of/O the/O dam/O project/O ./O 
However/O due/O to/O strong/O legal/O opposition/O from/O villagers/O and/O his/O wife/O the/O engineer/O leaves/O the/O dam/O unbuilt/O ./O 
Years/O later/O after/O the/O death/O of/O the/O engineer/O his/O son/O fulfills/O his/O father/O s/O dream/O keeping/O in/O mind/O the/O cause/O of/O the/O villagers/O and/O the/O struggle/O of/O his/O mother/O and/O also/O fights/O against/O corporates/O who/O are/O trying/O to/O exploit/O the/O dam/O for/O their/O monetary/O benefit/O ./O 
Monty/PERSON Brewster/PERSON is/O a/O second/O rate/O minor/O league/O baseball/O pitcher/O with/O the/O Hackensack/ORGANIZATION Bulls/ORGANIZATION ./O 
He/O and/O his/O best/O friend/O Spike/PERSON Nolan/PERSON the/O catcher/O for/O the/O Bulls/O are/O arrested/O and/O can/O not/O afford/O bail/O ./O 
A/O stranger/O offers/O bail/O if/O they/O will/O come/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City/LOCATION with/O him/O ./O 
At/O the/O Manhattan/LOCATION law/O office/O of/O Granville/PERSON Baxter/PERSON Brewster/PERSON is/O told/O that/O his/O recently/O deceased/O great/O uncle/O Rupert/PERSON Horn/PERSON whom/O he/O has/O never/O met/O has/O left/O him/O his/O entire/O fortune/O but/O with/O several/O conditions/O ./O 
Brewster/PERSON is/O challenged/O to/O either/O take/O 1/O million/O upfront/O or/O spend/O 3/O 0/O million/O within/O 3/O 0/O days/O to/O inherit/O 3/O 0/O 0/O million/O ./O 
If/O he/O chooses/O the/O former/O the/O law/O firm/O becomes/O the/O executor/O of/O the/O estate/O and/O divides/O the/O money/O among/O charities/O ./O 
In/O the/O latter/O case/O after/O 3/O 0/O days/O he/O may/O not/O own/O any/O assets/O that/O are/O not/O already/O his/O and/O he/O must/O get/O value/O for/O the/O services/O of/O anyone/O he/O hires/O ./O 
He/O may/O donate/O only/O 5/O to/O charity/O and/O lose/O 5/O by/O gambling/O ./O 
And/O he/O is/O not/O allowed/O to/O tell/O anyone/O even/O Spike/PERSON ./O 
Monty/PERSON decides/O to/O take/O the/O 3/O 0/O million/O challenge/O ./O 
Angela/PERSON Drake/PERSON a/O paralegal/O from/O the/O law/O firm/O must/O accompany/O him/O to/O keep/O tabs/O on/O all/O spending/O ./O 
Monty/PERSON who/O has/O no/O concept/O of/O money/O rents/O an/O expensive/O hotel/O suite/O hires/O personal/O staff/O on/O exorbitant/O salaries/O and/O places/O bad/O bets/O ./O 
But/O Spike/PERSON invests/O his/O money/O wisely/O earning/O Brewster/PERSON money/O ./O 
Brewster/PERSON realizing/O he/O is/O right/O back/O where/O he/O started/O gets/O the/O idea/O to/O join/O the/O race/O for/O Mayor/O of/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION and/O throws/O most/O of/O his/O money/O at/O a/O protest/O campaign/O urging/O a/O vote/O for/O None/O of/O the/O Above/O ./O 
The/O two/O major/O candidates/O threaten/O to/O sue/O Brewster/PERSON for/O his/O confrontational/O rhetoric/O but/O they/O settle/O out/O of/O court/O for/O several/O million/O dollars/O ./O 
Brewster/PERSON then/O hires/O the/O New/ORGANIZATION York/ORGANIZATION Yankees/ORGANIZATION for/O a/O three/O inning/O exhibition/O against/O his/O Hackensack/LOCATION team/O with/O himself/O as/O the/O pitcher/O ./O 
He/O is/O forced/O to/O end/O his/O protest/O campaign/O when/O he/O learns/O that/O he/O is/O leading/O in/O the/O polls/O as/O a/O write/O in/O candidate/O and/O should/O he/O win/O the/O job/O would/O carry/O a/O 6/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O annual/O salary/O which/O is/O an/O asset/O by/O the/O terms/O of/O the/O will/O ./O 
Blowing/O his/O last/O 3/O 8/O 0/O 0/O 0/O on/O a/O party/O after/O the/O game/O Brewster/PERSON becomes/O fed/O up/O with/O money/O and/O is/O heartbroken/O that/O Spike/PERSON Angela/PERSON and/O others/O around/O him/O do/O not/O understand/O his/O actions/O ./O 
On/O the/O 3/O 0/O th/O day/O he/O finds/O that/O the/O sycophantic/O treatment/O he/O received/O from/O his/O entourage/O is/O gone/O and/O he/O makes/O his/O way/O to/O the/O law/O office/O ./O 
Having/O withdrawn/O from/O the/O election/O he/O learns/O that/O the/O city/O voted/O None/O of/O the/O Above/O forcing/O another/O election/O with/O none/O of/O the/O candidates/O running/O for/O office/O again/O ./O 
Warren/PERSON Cox/PERSON a/O junior/O lawyer/O from/O the/O law/O firm/O and/O Angela/PERSON s/O fiancee/O has/O been/O bribed/O by/O the/O firm/O to/O ensure/O Brewster/PERSON fails/O to/O spend/O the/O entire/O 3/O 0/O million/O ./O 
Moments/O before/O time/O expires/O Warren/PERSON hands/O Monty/O some/O money/O previously/O thought/O to/O have/O been/O spent/O and/O informs/O him/O he/O is/O not/O broke/O ./O 
Brewster/PERSON punches/O Warren/PERSON who/O threatens/O to/O sue/O ./O 
Realizing/O he/O will/O need/O a/O lawyer/O he/O pays/O Angela/PERSON a/O 2/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O retainer/O ./O 
At/O the/O very/O last/O second/O Brewster/PERSON now/O complied/O with/O the/O conditions/O and/O inherits/O the/O 3/O 0/O 0/O million/O ./O 
In/O December/O 1/O 9/O 5/O 8/O Norville/ORGANIZATION Barnes/ORGANIZATION a/O business/O college/O graduate/O from/O Muncie/LOCATION Indiana/LOCATION arrives/O in/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City/LOCATION looking/O for/O a/O job/O ./O 
He/O struggles/O due/O to/O lack/O of/O experience/O and/O becomes/O a/O mailroom/O clerk/O at/O Hudsucker/ORGANIZATION Industries/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Meanwhile/O the/O company/O founder/O and/O president/O Waring/ORGANIZATION Hudsucker/ORGANIZATION unexpectedly/O commits/O suicide/O by/O jumping/O out/O of/O a/O top/O floor/O window/O ./O 
When/O Sidney/PERSON J/PERSON Mussburger/PERSON a/O ruthless/O member/O of/O the/O board/O of/O directors/O learns/O that/O Hudsucker/ORGANIZATION s/O stock/O shares/O will/O be/O sold/O to/O the/O public/O soon/O he/O mounts/O a/O scheme/O to/O buy/O the/O controlling/O interest/O in/O the/O company/O he/O will/O temporarily/O depress/O the/O stock/O price/O by/O hiring/O an/O incompetent/O president/O to/O replace/O Hudsucker/O ./O 
Shortly/O before/O his/O last/O meeting/O Hudsucker/O sent/O Mussburger/PERSON a/O top/O secret/O communication/O called/O a/O Blue/O Letter/O which/O Norville/PERSON is/O assigned/O to/O deliver/O ./O 
After/O meeting/O Norville/PERSON Mussburger/PERSON selects/O him/O as/O a/O proxy/O for/O Hudsucker/O ./O 
Across/O town/O Amy/PERSON Archer/PERSON a/O brassy/O Pulitzer/O Prize/O winning/O reporter/O for/O the/O Manhattan/LOCATION Argus/LOCATION is/O assigned/O to/O write/O a/O story/O about/O Norville/PERSON and/O find/O out/O what/O kind/O of/O man/O he/O really/O is/O ./O 
She/O gets/O a/O job/O at/O Hudsucker/ORGANIZATION Industries/ORGANIZATION as/O his/O personal/O secretary/O pretending/O to/O be/O yet/O another/O desperate/O graduate/O from/O Muncie/LOCATION ./O 
One/O night/O Amy/PERSON searches/O the/O building/O to/O find/O clues/O and/O meets/O Moses/PERSON a/O man/O who/O operates/O the/O tower/O s/O giant/O clock/O and/O knows/O just/O about/O anything/O if/O it/O concerns/O Hudsucker/O ./O 
He/O tells/O her/O Mussburger/PERSON s/O plot/O and/O she/O takes/O the/O story/O back/O to/O her/O Chief/O but/O he/O does/O not/O believe/O a/O word/O of/O it/O ./O 
The/O other/O executives/O decide/O to/O accept/O Norville/PERSON s/O invention/O for/O the/O hula/O hoop/O in/O the/O hope/O that/O it/O will/O depress/O the/O company/O s/O stock/O ./O 
However/O the/O hula/O hoop/O brings/O the/O company/O greater/O success/O than/O before/O ./O 
Amy/PERSON is/O infuriated/O over/O Norville/PERSON s/O new/O attitude/O and/O leaves/O him/O ./O 
Buzz/O the/O eager/O elevator/O operator/O pitches/O a/O new/O invention/O the/O flexi/O straw/O ./O 
Norville/PERSON does/O not/O like/O it/O and/O fires/O Buzz/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O the/O Hudsucker/ORGANIZATION janitor/O Aloysius/PERSON discovers/O Amy/PERSON s/O true/O identity/O and/O informs/O Mussburger/PERSON ./O 
Mussburger/PERSON reveals/O Amy/PERSON s/O secret/O identity/O to/O Norville/PERSON and/O tells/O him/O that/O he/O will/O be/O dismissed/O as/O president/O after/O the/O new/O year/O ./O 
Mussburger/PERSON also/O convinces/O the/O board/O that/O Norville/PERSON is/O insane/O and/O must/O be/O sent/O to/O the/O local/O psychiatric/O hospital/O ./O 
On/O New/O Year/O s/O Eve/PERSON Amy/PERSON finds/O Norville/PERSON drunk/O at/O a/O beatnik/O bar/O ./O 
She/O apologizes/O but/O he/O storms/O out/O and/O is/O chased/O by/O an/O angry/O mob/O led/O by/O Buzz/PERSON who/O was/O led/O by/O Mussburger/PERSON to/O believe/O that/O Norville/PERSON stole/O the/O hula/O hoop/O idea/O ./O 
Norville/PERSON escapes/O to/O the/O top/O floor/O of/O the/O Hudsucker/O skyscraper/O and/O changes/O back/O into/O his/O mailroom/O uniform/O ./O 
He/O climbs/O out/O on/O the/O ledge/O where/O Aloysius/PERSON locks/O out/O Norville/PERSON and/O watches/O as/O he/O slips/O and/O falls/O off/O the/O building/O at/O the/O stroke/O of/O midnight/O ./O 
All/O of/O a/O sudden/O Moses/O stops/O the/O clock/O and/O time/O freezes/O ./O 
Waring/ORGANIZATION Hudsucker/ORGANIZATION appears/O to/O Norville/PERSON as/O an/O angel/O and/O tells/O him/O that/O the/O Blue/O Letter/O that/O was/O supposed/O to/O be/O delivered/O to/O Mussburger/PERSON contains/O a/O legal/O document/O indicating/O that/O Hudsucker/ORGANIZATION s/O shares/O would/O go/O to/O his/O immediate/O successor/O which/O is/O now/O Norville/PERSON ./O 
Moses/O fights/O and/O defeats/O Aloysius/PERSON inside/O the/O tower/O allowing/O Norville/PERSON to/O fall/O safely/O to/O the/O ground/O ./O 
Norville/PERSON and/O Amy/PERSON reconcile/O ./O 
As/O 1/O 9/O 5/O 9/O progresses/O it/O is/O Mussburger/PERSON who/O is/O sent/O to/O the/O asylum/O while/O Norville/PERSON develops/O a/O new/O invention/O for/O kids/O a/O flying/O disc/O of/O some/O kind/O that/O will/O ultimately/O turn/O out/O to/O be/O a/O frisbee/O ./O 
The/O film/O opens/O in/O a/O very/O grungy/O broken/O obviously/O destitute/O ghetto/O area/O where/O we/O see/O a/O half/O naked/O man/O laboriously/O two/O finger/O pecking/O at/O an/O old/O typewriter/O ./O 
We/O hear/O Remy/PERSON in/O the/O third/O person/O musing/O on/O the/O fate/O of/O Schrodinger/PERSON s/O cat/O ./O 
In/O 2/O 0/O 2/O 5/O a/O corporation/O called/O The/O Union/O has/O perfected/O the/O creation/O of/O bio/O mechanical/O organs/O which/O are/O available/O to/O those/O with/O money/O or/O good/O credit/O ./O 
If/O a/O customer/O falls/O three/O months/O behind/O on/O payments/O a/O repo/O man/O is/O sent/O to/O reclaim/O the/O artificial/O organ/O ./O 
The/O process/O of/O the/O repossession/O almost/O always/O results/O in/O the/O death/O of/O the/O customer/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON and/O his/O partner/O Jake/PERSON Freivald/PERSON are/O considered/O the/O best/O of/O the/O Union/O s/O repo/O men/O ./O 
This/O causes/O personal/O issues/O between/O Remy/PERSON and/O his/O wife/O Carol/PERSON forcing/O Remy/PERSON to/O consider/O a/O transfer/O to/O sales/O ./O 
After/O taking/O out/O a/O Nest/O a/O hideout/O of/O those/O who/O have/O fallen/O behind/O on/O credit/O Remy/PERSON and/O Jake/PERSON are/O asked/O by/O their/O boss/O Frank/PERSON Mercer/PERSON to/O become/O full/O time/O raid/O captains/O those/O who/O lead/O daily/O Nest/O raids/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON refuses/O and/O is/O about/O to/O ask/O Frank/PERSON about/O a/O job/O in/O sales/O but/O he/O is/O interrupted/O by/O Jake/PERSON ./O 
Later/O while/O driving/O Jake/PERSON tries/O to/O convince/O Remy/PERSON that/O their/O job/O is/O important/O regardless/O of/O the/O moral/O issues/O ./O 
Still/O attempting/O to/O save/O his/O marriage/O with/O a/O transfer/O to/O sales/O Jake/PERSON tells/O Remy/PERSON that/O his/O last/O job/O should/O be/O a/O cardiac/O repossession/O from/O a/O musician/O named/O T/O Bone/O of/O whom/O Remy/PERSON is/O a/O big/O fan/O ./O 
The/O repo/O requires/O the/O use/O of/O a/O defibrillator/O ./O 
The/O device/O malfunctions/O and/O Remy/PERSON is/O violently/O shocked/O and/O severely/O injured/O ./O 
The/O damage/O requires/O the/O replacement/O of/O his/O own/O heart/O with/O an/O artiforg/O heart/O ./O 
Carol/PERSON divorces/O Remy/PERSON so/O he/O moves/O in/O temporarily/O with/O Jake/PERSON ./O 
he/O is/O unable/O to/O lie/O to/O potential/O costumers/O about/O the/O consequences/O of/O non/O payment/O and/O loses/O most/O of/O his/O commissions/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON is/O forced/O back/O into/O repo/O to/O pay/O for/O his/O heart/O ./O 
But/O due/O to/O his/O own/O artificial/O organ/O he/O develops/O sympathy/O with/O his/O victims/O leaving/O him/O unable/O to/O perform/O his/O job/O and/O earn/O any/O money/O ./O 
When/O Jake/PERSON discovers/O that/O Remy/PERSON has/O not/O been/O repossessing/O he/O takes/O him/O to/O another/O nest/O to/O find/O enough/O artiforgs/O to/O clear/O his/O debt/O and/O get/O over/O his/O inability/O to/O repossess/O ./O 
However/O Remy/PERSON still/O can/O not/O find/O it/O to/O do/O his/O job/O ./O 
Jake/PERSON stuns/O two/O insolvents/O and/O insists/O that/O Remy/PERSON stay/O and/O finish/O the/O repossessions/O until/O he/O gets/O over/O his/O Hump/O ./O 
During/O Remy/PERSON s/O deliberations/O with/O his/O conscience/O a/O debtor/O revives/O and/O beats/O him/O unconscious/O ./O 
Upon/O awakening/O Remy/PERSON encounters/O Beth/PERSON who/O is/O past/O due/O on/O multiple/O organ/O transplants/O ./O 
After/O a/O failed/O attempt/O to/O clear/O both/O their/O individual/O accounts/O back/O at/O the/O Union/O s/O local/O headquarters/O Remy/O torches/O his/O car/O and/O anything/O else/O traceable/O before/O the/O two/O leave/O to/O live/O in/O the/O outskirts/O ./O 
Beth/PERSON gifts/O him/O with/O an/O old/O manual/O typewriter/O and/O Remy/PERSON decides/O to/O document/O his/O life/O as/O a/O repo/O man/O ./O 
The/O typing/O process/O is/O a/O flashback/O to/O the/O opening/O scene/O of/O the/O film/O ./O 
As/O he/O works/O he/O is/O interrupted/O by/O the/O arrival/O of/O another/O repo/O man/O identified/O earlier/O in/O the/O film/O as/O a/O rather/O pathetic/O level/O 3/O collector/O intending/O to/O repossess/O his/O heart/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON sets/O a/O trap/O and/O drops/O him/O three/O stories/O through/O a/O hole/O in/O the/O floor/O ./O 
The/O floor/O then/O gives/O way/O so/O Beth/PERSON accidentally/O falls/O through/O the/O same/O hole/O and/O her/O prosthetic/O knee/O gets/O badly/O damaged/O ./O 
The/O level/O 3/O collector/O is/O about/O to/O shoot/O Beth/PERSON so/O Remy/PERSON ultimately/O drops/O the/O typewriter/O on/O his/O head/O ./O 
Using/O the/O repo/O man/O s/O vehicle/O Remy/PERSON sneaks/O back/O into/O his/O former/O workplace/O to/O obtain/O a/O pair/O of/O jamming/O devices/O that/O fool/O organ/O scanners/O used/O by/O repo/O men/O ./O 
He/O attempts/O to/O force/O Frank/PERSON to/O clear/O his/O account/O only/O to/O discover/O that/O due/O to/O his/O prior/O attempt/O all/O accounts/O can/O only/O be/O cleared/O back/O at/O the/O Union/O s/O central/O office/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON and/O Beth/PERSON attempt/O to/O flee/O the/O country/O at/O the/O airport/O but/O are/O taken/O by/O security/O when/O the/O bleeding/O from/O Beth/PERSON s/O knee/O leaves/O a/O significant/O pool/O on/O the/O floor/O ./O 
A/O major/O fight/O with/O airport/O security/O ensues/O ./O 
Jake/PERSON has/O been/O put/O on/O their/O trail/O after/O the/O failure/O of/O the/O earlier/O repo/O attempt/O ./O 
He/O finds/O them/O at/O the/O airport/O but/O is/O on/O the/O wrong/O side/O of/O a/O security/O panel/O and/O can/O only/O watch/O their/O escape/O ./O 
The/O pair/O head/O to/O a/O black/O market/O doctor/O where/O Beth/PERSON s/O knee/O is/O replaced/O ./O 
After/O the/O procedure/O the/O two/O are/O stopped/O by/O Jake/PERSON who/O has/O tracked/O the/O pair/O ./O 
A/O bitter/O fight/O ensues/O during/O which/O it/O is/O revealed/O that/O it/O was/O Jake/PERSON that/O rigged/O the/O defibrillator/O unit/O to/O fail/O causing/O Remy/PERSON s/O heart/O replacement/O he/O did/O this/O to/O ensure/O that/O Remy/PERSON keeps/O his/O organ/O repossession/O job/O so/O they/O could/O get/O promoted/O ./O 
The/O two/O fight/O but/O Jake/PERSON wins/O the/O fight/O fairly/O decisively/O ./O 
During/O a/O pause/O for/O manic/O laughter/O Remy/PERSON simultaneously/O stabs/O Jake/PERSON above/O the/O knee/O while/O Jake/PERSON knocks/O Remy/PERSON unconscious/O with/O a/O heavy/O steel/O hook/O and/O Beth/PERSON shoots/O Jake/PERSON with/O his/O stun/O pistol/O ./O 
After/O a/O sequence/O of/O phantasmagorical/O flashbacks/O Beth/PERSON awakens/O Remy/PERSON and/O they/O become/O aware/O that/O an/O organ/O repossession/O raid/O is/O underway/O ./O 
They/O flee/O with/O the/O other/O residents/O of/O the/O ghetto/O and/O accidentally/O stumble/O upon/O a/O scan/O blocked/O refuge/O with/O a/O small/O fraction/O of/O the/O other/O residents/O ./O 
After/O an/O indeterminate/O period/O of/O rest/O and/O sleep/O Remy/PERSON leaves/O the/O refuge/O to/O find/O dozens/O of/O the/O other/O occupants/O slain/O and/O eviscerated/O by/O the/O Union/O s/O repo/O men/O ./O 
He/O resolves/O to/O destroy/O the/O corporation/O and/O delete/O all/O accounts/O of/O all/O Union/O implanted/O individuals/O We/O wipe/O the/O system/O ./O 
No/O more/O accounts/O ./O 
No/O one/O s/O overdue/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON passes/O his/O manuscript/O to/O his/O son/O during/O a/O brief/O meeting/O on/O a/O train/O ./O 
The/O pair/O then/O travel/O to/O The/O Union/O s/O headquarters/O hoping/O to/O fulfill/O their/O pledge/O to/O wipe/O the/O system/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON and/O Beth/PERSON are/O pursued/O throughout/O the/O building/O and/O after/O an/O intense/O battle/O arrive/O at/O the/O Pink/O Door/O the/O main/O database/O for/O the/O Union/O ./O 
Using/O Beth/PERSON s/O prosthetic/O eye/O they/O are/O able/O to/O seal/O themselves/O inside/O just/O as/O Jake/PERSON and/O Frank/PERSON arrive/O ./O 
Once/O inside/O they/O discover/O that/O the/O server/O does/O not/O have/O any/O interface/O other/O than/O an/O organ/O scanner/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON realizes/O that/O the/O only/O modifications/O they/O can/O make/O to/O the/O system/O are/O with/O what/O they/O brought/O in/O themselves/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON and/O Beth/PERSON take/O turns/O cutting/O themselves/O open/O in/O order/O to/O use/O the/O scanner/O internally/O clearing/O their/O own/O accounts/O ./O 
Jake/PERSON and/O Frank/PERSON are/O able/O to/O enter/O through/O the/O use/O of/O an/O organ/O scavenged/O from/O a/O victim/O of/O Remy/PERSON s/O earlier/O fight/O and/O catch/O Remy/PERSON trying/O desperately/O to/O scan/O Beth/PERSON s/O last/O overdue/O organ/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON tells/O them/O that/O he/O is/O losing/O her/O ./O 
Jake/PERSON asks/O Remy/PERSON if/O she/O is/O worth/O it/O to/O which/O he/O responds/O She/O s/O worth/O every/O job/O that/O we/O ever/O did/O ./O 
Frank/PERSON pulls/O a/O gun/O to/O kill/O Remy/PERSON but/O Jake/PERSON turns/O on/O his/O employer/O killing/O him/O with/O a/O knife/O ./O 
Jake/PERSON then/O assists/O Remy/PERSON in/O reviving/O Beth/PERSON after/O which/O he/O deposits/O two/O explosives/O inside/O the/O organ/O retrieval/O unit/O in/O lieu/O of/O the/O many/O organs/O previously/O scanned/O ./O 
The/O explosion/O destroys/O the/O Union/O s/O mainframe/O wiping/O everyone/O who/O has/O an/O account/O with/O the/O corporation/O out/O of/O the/O system/O ./O 
Later/O Remy/O is/O on/O a/O tropical/O beach/O enjoying/O his/O freedom/O with/O Beth/PERSON and/O Jake/PERSON ./O 
His/O text/O from/O earlier/O in/O the/O film/O has/O been/O published/O into/O a/O book/O The/O Repossession/O Mambo/O ./O 
Remy/PERSON turns/O to/O look/O at/O Jake/PERSON but/O sees/O instead/O the/O background/O flickering/O and/O incoherent/O voices/O ./O 
It/O is/O discovered/O that/O Remy/PERSON in/O fact/O sustained/O severe/O brain/O damage/O when/O Jake/PERSON hit/O him/O with/O the/O heavy/O hook/O earlier/O in/O the/O film/O ./O 
Jake/PERSON out/O of/O remorse/O has/O paid/O off/O Remy/PERSON s/O account/O and/O has/O had/O him/O placed/O in/O a/O neural/O network/O allowing/O him/O to/O live/O the/O rest/O of/O his/O life/O in/O a/O dream/O ./O 
Beth/PERSON is/O still/O alive/O but/O unconscious/O and/O when/O questioned/O as/O to/O what/O to/O do/O with/O her/O Jake/PERSON says/O he/O will/O take/O care/O of/O her/O ./O 
This/O renders/O the/O ending/O sequence/O of/O the/O film/O as/O simply/O a/O fantasy/O of/O Remy/PERSON s/O Jake/PERSON finds/O Remy/PERSON s/O manuscript/O which/O he/O greets/O with/O a/O sad/O stifled/O sigh/O as/O his/O former/O partner/O is/O wheeled/O away/O presumably/O to/O spend/O the/O rest/O of/O his/O life/O in/O his/O fantasy/O world/O ./O 
The/O film/O ends/O with/O Frank/PERSON delivering/O a/O sales/O pitch/O for/O the/O neural/O network/O ./O 
Molly/PERSON Thatcher/PERSON is/O a/O stockbroker/O languishing/O in/O a/O company/O run/O by/O sexist/O Bullard/ORGANIZATION Bear/ORGANIZATION ./O 
When/O the/O company/O does/O poorly/O he/O has/O to/O fire/O somebody/O ./O 
Molly/PERSON is/O the/O obvious/O choice/O but/O to/O avoid/O charges/O of/O sex/O discrimination/O he/O assigns/O her/O the/O seemingly/O impossible/O task/O of/O unloading/O shares/O of/O an/O obscure/O company/O called/O Universal/ORGANIZATION Widgets/ORGANIZATION figuring/O that/O when/O she/O fails/O he/O will/O have/O an/O excuse/O to/O dismiss/O her/O ./O 
Molly/PERSON meets/O Henry/PERSON Tyroon/PERSON an/O aggressive/O wheeler/O dealer/O who/O dresses/O talks/O and/O acts/O like/O a/O stereotypical/O Texas/LOCATION millionaire/O ./O 
He/O s/O more/O interested/O in/O her/O than/O in/O Universal/O Widgets/O but/O decides/O to/O help/O in/O order/O to/O get/O closer/O to/O her/O ./O 
As/O they/O spend/O time/O together/O Molly/PERSON watches/O Henry/PERSON make/O complicated/O business/O deals/O often/O in/O partnership/O with/O his/O Texan/O cronies/O Jay/PERSON Ray/PERSON Ray/PERSON Jay/PERSON and/O JR/O One/O such/O deal/O is/O a/O venture/O into/O dealing/O modern/O art/O with/O the/O aid/O of/O Stanislas/PERSON a/O cynical/O avant/O garde/O painter/O ./O 
Molly/PERSON and/O Henry/PERSON have/O trouble/O figuring/O out/O Universal/O Widgets/O reason/O for/O existence/O its/O only/O factory/O burned/O down/O around/O the/O time/O of/O the/O Civil/O War/O it/O manufactures/O nothing/O and/O provides/O no/O service/O ./O 
It/O s/O just/O a/O corporation/O on/O paper/O whose/O sole/O asset/O is/O a/O huge/O block/O of/O shares/O in/O ATT/ORGANIZATION bought/O long/O long/O ago/O when/O it/O was/O ridiculously/O cheap/O ./O 
Now/O it/O pays/O hefty/O regular/O dividends/O to/O its/O complacent/O shareholders/O ./O 
When/O Henry/PERSON makes/O an/O attempt/O to/O take/O control/O of/O the/O undervalued/O company/O by/O questionable/O methods/O over/O enthusiastic/O government/O regulator/O Hector/PERSON Vanson/PERSON takes/O him/O to/O court/O ./O 
Further/O complications/O arise/O when/O Jay/PERSON Ray/PERSON Ray/PERSON Jay/PERSON and/O JR/O get/O Molly/PERSON fired/O so/O she/O can/O spend/O more/O time/O with/O Henry/PERSON she/O thinks/O Henry/PERSON is/O responsible/O ./O 
The/O case/O is/O dismissed/O when/O it/O is/O determined/O that/O all/O the/O shares/O are/O in/O the/O hands/O of/O a/O few/O people/O not/O the/O general/O public/O ./O 
The/O Texans/O are/O bought/O out/O ./O 
Once/O the/O Texas/LOCATION trio/O confess/O that/O they/O got/O Molly/PERSON fired/O she/O and/O Henry/PERSON make/O up/O ./O 
An/O evil/O businessman/O is/O secretly/O setting/O fires/O to/O some/O of/O the/O old/O buildings/O of/O a/O dilapidated/O neighborhood/O while/O at/O the/O same/O time/O three/O women/O become/O the/O new/O recruits/O at/O a/O local/O fire/O station/O ./O 
Life/O is/O not/O smooth/O at/O the/O new/O firehouse/O as/O the/O women/O are/O teased/O and/O harassed/O by/O their/O male/O coworkers/O ./O 
But/O they/O learn/O to/O stand/O up/O for/O themselves/O against/O the/O torment/O while/O also/O solving/O the/O mystery/O of/O who/O is/O starting/O the/O fires/O ./O 
Leung/PERSON plays/O Jennifer/PERSON the/O spoiled/O rotten/O daughter/O of/O a/O millionaire/O ./O 
When/O Jennifer/PERSON s/O father/O realizes/O that/O she/O s/O spending/O way/O too/O much/O money/O he/O hires/O Kit/O to/O pretend/O to/O be/O a/O Filipino/O chauffeur/O and/O chaperone/O her/O ./O 
Then/O Jennifer/PERSON s/O father/O decides/O that/O he/O s/O going/O to/O teach/O her/O the/O value/O of/O money/O and/O hard/O work/O so/O he/O pretends/O to/O be/O ill/O leaving/O all/O the/O money/O to/O Pamela/PERSON his/O business/O partner/O ./O 
Pamela/PERSON kicks/O Jennifer/PERSON out/O into/O the/O street/O to/O live/O with/O Kit/PERSON Mario/PERSON ./O 
The/O two/O learn/O to/O live/O together/O and/O work/O hard/O to/O get/O back/O on/O top/O ./O 
Marta/PERSON de/PERSON la/PERSON Cruz/PERSON is/O the/O daughter/O of/O two/O hardworking/O Mexican/O immigrants/O ./O 
She/O and/O her/O two/O siblings/O were/O born/O in/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION and/O are/O living/O in/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ./O 
They/O are/O a/O working/O class/O family/O and/O their/O hardworking/O father/O Samuel/PERSON is/O the/O opperations/O manager/O of/O a/O steel/O mill/O that/O makes/O chain/O link/O fences/O ./O 
He/O has/O been/O working/O hard/O for/O much/O of/O his/O life/O and/O the/O work/O finally/O paid/O off/O when/O they/O became/O legal/O citizens/O ./O 
They/O also/O have/O a/O close/O relationship/O with/O their/O next/O door/O neighbor/O Jorge/PERSON who/O is/O struggling/O to/O find/O work/O because/O he/O has/O no/O papers/O ./O 
Marta/PERSON is/O seen/O as/O spoiled/O immature/O and/O somewhat/O naive/O but/O she/O wants/O to/O have/O an/O amazing/O quinceanera/O as/O her/O friends/O are/O all/O having/O one/O ./O 
Her/O parents/O tell/O her/O that/O she/O may/O have/O to/O postpone/O it/O because/O of/O financial/O problems/O when/O in/O reality/O they/O are/O not/O legal/O citizens/O and/O they/O need/O to/O save/O money/O in/O case/O Samuel/PERSON s/O boss/O Mr/PERSON Waterman/PERSON finds/O out/O and/O he/O is/O left/O jobless/O ./O 
Marta/PERSON does/O not/O understand/O the/O situation/O and/O is/O very/O angry/O and/O upset/O ./O 
Her/O jealousy/O only/O increases/O when/O she/O is/O forced/O to/O get/O a/O job/O in/O the/O immigration/O department/O of/O their/O church/O to/O volunteer/O in/O the/O community/O ./O 
She/O continues/O to/O plan/O however/O determined/O to/O have/O her/O quince/O ./O 
Also/O her/O friends/O are/O busy/O hitting/O on/O her/O handsome/O distant/O cousin/O Ramon/PERSON from/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION who/O just/O arrived/O in/O California/LOCATION ./O 
They/O are/O pressuring/O Marta/PERSON to/O dance/O with/O him/O at/O her/O quince/O but/O she/O is/O too/O shy/O and/O Ramon/PERSON is/O struggling/O with/O his/O inability/O to/O read/O or/O write/O ./O 
Samuel/PERSON knows/O that/O he/O has/O earned/O his/O citizenship/O as/O he/O has/O worked/O hard/O and/O lived/O in/O America/LOCATION for/O over/O a/O decade/O but/O as/O he/O has/O no/O papers/O there/O is/O no/O way/O that/O anybody/O can/O know/O that/O ./O 
While/O working/O at/O the/O church/O one/O day/O Marta/PERSON discovers/O that/O Samuel/PERSON is/O an/O illegal/O and/O begins/O getting/O very/O worried/O and/O touchy/O about/O the/O subject/O ./O 
The/O same/O day/O despite/O Samuel/PERSON s/O warnings/O Jorge/PERSON gets/O a/O job/O at/O a/O warehouse/O that/O has/O a/O reputation/O for/O deporting/O illegal/O employes/O on/O pay/O day/O ./O 
Samuel/PERSON does/O not/O want/O Marta/PERSON dating/O Ramon/PERSON but/O she/O goes/O behind/O his/O back/O and/O enlists/O him/O for/O help/O in/O getting/O all/O of/O Samuel/PERSON s/O previous/O employer/O s/O signatures/O so/O he/O can/O get/O his/O papers/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O Jorge/PERSON is/O deported/O to/O Mexico/LOCATION when/O he/O fails/O to/O present/O his/O papers/O which/O he/O does/O not/O have/O ./O 
Also/O at/O Samuel/PERSON s/O plant/O more/O and/O more/O employees/O are/O being/O fired/O or/O deported/O and/O Samuel/PERSON fears/O he/O may/O be/O next/O so/O he/O is/O hard/O at/O work/O trying/O to/O find/O a/O second/O job/O one/O that/O does/O not/O require/O papers/O ./O 
She/O gets/O all/O but/O one/O signature/O and/O goes/O to/O an/O auto/O salvage/O yard/O for/O the/O last/O one/O but/O the/O manager/O is/O rude/O and/O stubbornly/O refuses/O to/O sign/O the/O papers/O ./O 
Marta/PERSON is/O persistant/O and/O the/O manager/O has/O a/O change/O of/O heart/O and/O manages/O to/O sign/O the/O papers/O ./O 
Also/O Ramon/PERSON learns/O how/O to/O read/O and/O surprises/O Marta/PERSON with/O it/O ./O 
She/O presents/O her/O father/O with/O his/O signatures/O and/O he/O sends/O them/O in/O for/O their/O papers/O ./O 
Soon/O after/O he/O is/O given/O his/O temporary/O papers/O to/O show/O at/O his/O job/O as/O it/O will/O be/O a/O while/O before/O their/O permanent/O papers/O arrive/O ./O 
Samuel/PERSON thanks/O his/O daughter/O and/O they/O embrace/O ./O 
However/O Marta/PERSON is/O soon/O told/O that/O they/O found/O that/O she/O had/O been/O tampering/O with/O the/O files/O and/O she/O has/O to/O go/O inside/O ./O 
As/O she/O goes/O in/O expecting/O the/O worst/O she/O discovers/O that/O it/O was/O all/O part/O of/O her/O surprise/O quince/O ./O 
She/O dances/O with/O Ramon/PERSON whom/O her/O father/O now/O respects/O ./O 
Marta/PERSON having/O grown/O up/O and/O changed/O considerably/O from/O spoiled/O to/O respectful/O during/O the/O journey/O she/O embraces/O her/O newlyfound/O womanhood/O ./O 
Stockbroker/O TR/PERSON Ralston/PERSON has/O promised/O his/O niece/O Gwen/PERSON he/O will/O double/O her/O monetary/O efforts/O to/O benefit/O a/O local/O charity/O ./O 
She/O goes/O behind/O his/O back/O in/O order/O to/O increase/O her/O final/O output/O ./O 
To/O complicate/O matters/O Bennett/PERSON uses/O Gwen/PERSON s/O money/O to/O make/O a/O bet/O with/O Ralston/PERSON and/O his/O fellow/O work/O associates/O he/O must/O tell/O the/O truth/O for/O the/O next/O 2/O 4/O hours/O ./O 
When/O the/O Manhattan/LOCATION investment/O firm/O of/O Sherwood/PERSON Nash/PERSON goes/O broke/O he/O joins/O forces/O with/O his/O partner/O Snap/PERSON and/O fashion/O designer/O Lynn/PERSON Mason/PERSON to/O provide/O discount/O shops/O with/O cheap/O copies/O of/O Paris/LOCATION couture/O dresses/O ./O 
Lynn/PERSON discovers/O that/O top/O designer/O Oscar/PERSON Baroque/PERSON gets/O his/O inspiration/O from/O old/O costume/O books/O and/O she/O begins/O to/O create/O designs/O the/O same/O way/O signing/O each/O one/O with/O the/O name/O of/O an/O established/O designer/O ./O 
Sherwood/PERSON realizes/O Baroque/O s/O companion/O the/O alleged/O Grand/O Duchess/O Alix/O is/O really/O Mabel/PERSON McGuire/PERSON his/O old/O friend/O from/O Hoboken/LOCATION New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION and/O threatens/O to/O reveal/O her/O identity/O unless/O she/O convinces/O Baroque/O to/O design/O the/O costumes/O of/O a/O musical/O revue/O in/O which/O she/O will/O star/O ./O 
Baroque/O buys/O a/O supply/O of/O ostrich/O feathers/O from/O Sherwood/PERSON s/O crony/O Joe/PERSON Ward/PERSON and/O starts/O a/O fashion/O rage/O ./O 
Sherwood/PERSON then/O opens/O Maison/PERSON Elegance/PERSON a/O new/O Paris/LOCATION fashion/O house/O that/O s/O a/O great/O success/O until/O Baroque/O discovers/O Lynn/PERSON is/O forging/O his/O sketches/O ./O 
He/O has/O him/O arrested/O but/O Sherwood/PERSON convinces/O the/O police/O to/O give/O him/O time/O to/O straighten/O out/O the/O situation/O ./O 
He/O crashes/O Baroque/O and/O Alix/PERSON s/O wedding/O and/O promises/O to/O humiliate/O the/O designer/O by/O publicly/O revealing/O who/O is/O bride/O really/O is/O unless/O Baroque/O withdraws/O the/O charges/O ./O 
The/O designer/O agrees/O and/O purchases/O Maison/ORGANIZATION Elegance/ORGANIZATION from/O Sherwood/PERSON who/O assures/O Lynn/PERSON he/O ll/O never/O get/O involved/O in/O another/O illegal/O activity/O if/O she/O returns/O to/O America/LOCATION with/O him/O ./O 
Milford/PERSON Farnsworth/PERSON is/O a/O bumbling/O insurance/O agent/O who/O unknowingly/O sells/O a/O life/O insurance/O policy/O to/O the/O outlaw/O Jesse/PERSON James/PERSON ./O 
Farnsworth/PERSON is/O sent/O out/O West/LOCATION to/O protect/O the/O insurance/O company/O s/O investment/O by/O protecting/O James/PERSON ./O 
James/PERSON has/O his/O own/O plans/O to/O have/O Farnsworth/PERSON killed/O while/O dressed/O as/O the/O outlaw/O so/O that/O he/O and/O his/O soon/O to/O be/O widow/O Cora/PERSON Lee/PERSON Collins/PERSON can/O collect/O on/O the/O 1/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O 0/O insurance/O policy/O ./O 
Farnsworth/PERSON avoids/O several/O attempts/O on/O his/O life/O while/O he/O and/O Collins/PERSON fall/O in/O love/O with/O each/O other/O ./O 
After/O the/O last/O attempt/O is/O made/O on/O his/O life/O Farnsworth/PERSON impersonates/O the/O justice/O of/O the/O peace/O who/O is/O supposed/O to/O marry/O James/PERSON and/O Collins/PERSON ./O 
When/O Farnsworth/PERSON and/O Collins/PERSON make/O a/O run/O for/O it/O they/O end/O up/O in/O a/O gun/O battle/O with/O the/O James/ORGANIZATION Gang/ORGANIZATION where/O several/O Western/O heroes/O make/O their/O cameos/O to/O surreptitiously/O help/O Farnsworth/PERSON ./O 
In/O the/O end/O Farnsworth/PERSON is/O victorious/O marries/O Collins/PERSON and/O becomes/O president/O of/O the/O insurance/O company/O ./O 
Ayesha/PERSON and/O Uday/PERSON Saxena/PERSON are/O a/O happily/O married/O couple/O living/O in/O Mumbai/LOCATION ./O 
Uday/PERSON a/O mechanical/O engineer/O works/O at/O a/O private/O company/O and/O they/O are/O living/O a/O perfect/O life/O with/O their/O four/O year/O old/O son/O Sunny/O ./O 
One/O day/O while/O coming/O back/O from/O a/O party/O they/O are/O involved/O in/O a/O major/O road/O accident/O in/O which/O the/O other/O driver/O dies/O on/O Ayeshas/O windshield/O an/O incident/O that/O plays/O on/O her/O mind/O and/O depresses/O her/O ./O 
When/O Uday/PERSON s/O boss/O offers/O him/O the/O job/O of/O managing/O a/O Jabalpur/LOCATION factory/O he/O accepts/O the/O opportunity/O to/O give/O Ayesha/PERSON a/O change/O of/O atmosphere/O ./O 
Uday/PERSON becomes/O busy/O with/O his/O job/O and/O rearranging/O their/O life/O ./O 
Ayesha/PERSON starts/O to/O feel/O the/O presence/O of/O someone/O in/O the/O house/O that/O no/O one/O else/O can/O ./O 
Her/O fears/O grow/O and/O she/O starts/O behaving/O in/O a/O bizarre/O manner/O ./O 
Homer/PERSON Smith/PERSON is/O an/O itinerant/O handyman/O jack/O of/O all/O trades/O who/O stops/O at/O a/O farm/O in/O the/O Arizona/LOCATION desert/O to/O obtain/O some/O water/O for/O his/O car/O ./O 
There/O he/O sees/O several/O women/O working/O on/O a/O fence/O very/O ineptly/O ./O 
The/O women/O who/O speak/O very/O little/O English/O introduce/O themselves/O as/O German/O Austrian/O and/O Hungarian/O nuns/O ./O 
The/O mother/O superior/O the/O leader/O of/O the/O nuns/O persuades/O him/O to/O do/O a/O small/O roofing/O repair/O ./O 
He/O stays/O overnight/O assuming/O that/O he/O will/O be/O paid/O in/O the/O morning/O ./O 
Next/O day/O Smith/PERSON tries/O to/O persuade/O the/O mother/O superior/O to/O pay/O him/O by/O quoting/O Luke/PERSON 1/O 0/O 7/O The/O laborer/O is/O worthy/O of/O his/O hire/O ./O 
Mother/O Maria/PERSON Marthe/PERSON responds/O by/O asking/O him/O to/O read/O another/O Bible/O verse/O from/O the/O Sermon/O on/O the/O Mount/O Consider/O the/O lilies/O of/O the/O field/O how/O they/O grow/O they/O toil/O not/O neither/O do/O they/O spin/O ./O 
And/O yet/O I/O say/O unto/O you/O that/O even/O Solomon/PERSON in/O all/O his/O glory/O was/O not/O arrayed/O like/O one/O of/O these/O ./O 
Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON likes/O things/O done/O her/O way/O ./O 
The/O nuns/O have/O essentially/O no/O money/O and/O subsist/O by/O living/O off/O the/O land/O on/O what/O vegetables/O the/O arid/O climate/O provides/O and/O some/O milk/O and/O eggs/O ./O 
Even/O after/O being/O stonewalled/O when/O asking/O for/O payment/O and/O after/O being/O persuaded/O to/O stay/O for/O a/O meal/O and/O against/O his/O better/O judgment/O Smith/PERSON agrees/O to/O stay/O another/O day/O to/O help/O them/O with/O other/O small/O jobs/O always/O with/O the/O faint/O hope/O that/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON will/O pay/O him/O for/O his/O work/O ./O 
As/O Smith/PERSON s/O skills/O and/O strengths/O become/O apparent/O to/O the/O nuns/O they/O come/O to/O believe/O that/O he/O has/O been/O sent/O by/O God/O to/O fulfill/O their/O dream/O of/O building/O a/O chapel/O for/O the/O townsfolk/O who/O are/O Mexican/O and/O impoverished/O as/O the/O nearest/O church/O is/O miles/O away/O ./O 
When/O Sunday/O comes/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON informs/O Smith/PERSON that/O he/O will/O be/O driving/O the/O sisters/O to/O Mass/O in/O his/O station/O wagon/O ./O 
Smith/PERSON is/O invited/O to/O attend/O the/O Catholic/O Mass/O but/O he/O declines/O because/O he/O is/O a/O Baptist/O ./O 
Instead/O he/O takes/O the/O opportunity/O to/O get/O a/O proper/O breakfast/O from/O the/O trading/O post/O next/O door/O ./O 
In/O talking/O to/O the/O proprietor/O Juan/PERSON Smith/PERSON learns/O about/O the/O hardships/O that/O the/O nuns/O led/O by/O the/O unyielding/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON overcame/O to/O emigrate/O from/O Eastern/LOCATION Europe/LOCATION over/O the/O Berlin/LOCATION Wall/LOCATION only/O to/O barely/O scratch/O out/O a/O meager/O living/O on/O the/O farm/O that/O was/O willed/O to/O their/O order/O ./O 
Though/O he/O has/O come/O to/O realize/O how/O unlikely/O it/O is/O that/O he/O will/O be/O paid/O and/O partly/O out/O of/O respect/O for/O all/O the/O women/O have/O overcome/O Smith/PERSON stays/O longer/O and/O finds/O himself/O driven/O to/O work/O on/O at/O least/O clearing/O the/O construction/O site/O for/O the/O chapel/O ./O 
He/O rationalizes/O that/O it/O would/O be/O too/O hard/O for/O the/O sisters/O to/O move/O the/O heavy/O beams/O ./O 
After/O losing/O another/O duel/O of/O Bible/O quotes/O with/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON Smith/PERSON acknowledges/O that/O he/O has/O always/O wanted/O to/O be/O an/O architect/O but/O couldn/O t/O afford/O the/O schooling/O ./O 
His/O unfulfilled/O dream/O impels/O him/O to/O agree/O to/O undertake/O the/O job/O of/O building/O the/O sisters/O a/O chapel/O ./O 
To/O earn/O money/O to/O buy/O some/O real/O food/O to/O supplement/O the/O spartan/O diet/O the/O nuns/O are/O able/O to/O provide/O him/O Smith/PERSON gets/O a/O part/O time/O job/O with/O the/O nearby/O construction/O contractor/O Ashton/PERSON who/O is/O impressed/O that/O Smith/PERSON can/O handle/O nearly/O every/O piece/O of/O heavy/O equipment/O he/O owns/O ./O 
Smith/PERSON supplements/O the/O nuns/O diet/O as/O well/O shopping/O for/O groceries/O to/O stock/O up/O their/O kitchen/O and/O delighting/O them/O with/O treats/O such/O as/O lollipops/O ./O 
To/O pass/O the/O evenings/O Smith/PERSON helps/O the/O sisters/O improve/O their/O rudimentary/O English/O and/O joins/O them/O in/O singing/O ./O 
They/O share/O their/O different/O musical/O traditions/O with/O one/O another/O their/O Catholic/O chants/O and/O his/O Baptist/O hymns/O ./O 
He/O teaches/O them/O to/O join/O him/O in/O the/O call/O and/O response/O song/O Amen/O by/O Jester/PERSON Hairston/PERSON ./O 
Smith/PERSON determined/O that/O the/O building/O will/O be/O constructed/O to/O the/O highest/O standards/O insists/O that/O the/O work/O be/O done/O by/O him/O and/O only/O him/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O the/O nuns/O write/O letters/O to/O various/O philanthropic/O organizations/O and/O charities/O asking/O for/O money/O for/O supplies/O but/O all/O their/O requests/O are/O denied/O ./O 
As/O word/O spreads/O about/O the/O endeavor/O locals/O begin/O to/O show/O up/O to/O contribute/O materials/O and/O to/O help/O in/O construction/O but/O Smith/PERSON rebuffs/O all/O offers/O of/O assistance/O in/O the/O labor/O ./O 
As/O he/O gains/O a/O larger/O and/O larger/O audience/O for/O his/O efforts/O the/O locals/O impressed/O with/O his/O determination/O but/O no/O less/O dogged/O than/O he/O will/O content/O themselves/O no/O longer/O with/O just/O watching/O ./O 
They/O find/O ways/O to/O lend/O a/O hand/O that/O Smith/PERSON can/O not/O easily/O turn/O down/O the/O lifting/O of/O a/O bucket/O or/O brick/O for/O example/O ./O 
Once/O the/O process/O is/O in/O motion/O they/O end/O up/O doing/O as/O they/O intended/O assisting/O in/O every/O aspect/O of/O the/O construction/O as/O well/O as/O contributing/O materials/O ./O 
This/O greatly/O accelerates/O the/O progress/O much/O to/O the/O delight/O of/O everyone/O but/O Smith/PERSON ./O 
Even/O Ashton/PERSON who/O has/O long/O ignored/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON s/O pleas/O finds/O an/O excuse/O to/O deliver/O some/O more/O materials/O ./O 
Almost/O overnight/O Smith/PERSON finds/O that/O he/O s/O become/O a/O building/O foreman/O and/O contractor/O ./O 
Enduring/O the/O hassles/O of/O coordinating/O the/O work/O of/O so/O many/O the/O constant/O disputes/O with/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON and/O the/O trial/O of/O getting/O enough/O materials/O for/O the/O building/O Smith/PERSON brings/O the/O chapel/O to/O completion/O placing/O the/O cross/O on/O the/O spire/O himself/O and/O signing/O his/O work/O where/O only/O he/O and/O God/O will/O know/O ./O 
It/O is/O the/O evening/O before/O the/O Sunday/O when/O the/O chapel/O is/O to/O be/O dedicated/O ./O 
All/O the/O work/O has/O been/O done/O and/O Smith/PERSON is/O exhausted/O ./O 
Now/O that/O there/O is/O nothing/O more/O to/O keep/O Smith/PERSON among/O them/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON too/O proud/O to/O ask/O him/O outright/O to/O stay/O insists/O that/O he/O attend/O the/O opening/O Mass/O next/O day/O to/O receive/O proper/O recognition/O from/O the/O congregation/O ./O 
She/O speaks/O enthusiastically/O of/O all/O that/O Schmidt/PERSON still/O can/O do/O to/O aid/O the/O town/O such/O as/O building/O a/O school/O ./O 
Making/O no/O reply/O to/O any/O of/O this/O Smith/PERSON tricks/O Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON as/O part/O of/O the/O night/O s/O English/O lesson/O into/O saying/O thank/O you/O to/O him/O ./O 
Until/O then/O she/O stubbornly/O had/O thanked/O only/O God/O for/O the/O work/O assistance/O and/O gifts/O that/O Smith/PERSON had/O provided/O to/O the/O nuns/O ./O 
It/O is/O a/O touching/O moment/O between/O two/O strong/O personalities/O ./O 
Later/O that/O evening/O as/O he/O leads/O the/O nuns/O in/O singing/O Amen/O once/O again/O Smith/PERSON slips/O out/O the/O door/O and/O still/O singing/O the/O lead/O the/O nuns/O voices/O chiming/O softly/O behind/O him/O he/O takes/O one/O last/O look/O at/O the/O chapel/O he/O built/O ./O 
Mother/PERSON Maria/PERSON hears/O him/O start/O up/O his/O station/O wagon/O but/O sits/O stoically/O singing/O along/O with/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O sisters/O as/O Smith/PERSON drives/O quietly/O off/O into/O the/O night/O ./O 
The/O movie/O was/O filmed/O on/O the/O northern/O edge/O of/O Tucson/LOCATION ./O 
The/O church/O doors/O were/O borrowed/O from/O the/O Chapel/O in/O Sasabe/LOCATION Arizona/LOCATION and/O were/O carved/O by/O local/O Tucson/LOCATION artist/O Charles/PERSON Bolsius/PERSON ./O 
David/PERSON and/O Linda/PERSON Howard/PERSON are/O typical/O 1/O 9/O 8/O 0/O s/O yuppies/O in/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION who/O are/O fed/O up/O with/O their/O lifestyle/O ./O 
He/O works/O in/O an/O advertising/O agency/O and/O she/O for/O a/O department/O store/O ./O 
But/O after/O he/O fails/O to/O receive/O a/O promotion/O he/O was/O counting/O on/O and/O is/O asked/O to/O transfer/O to/O the/O firm/O s/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION office/O instead/O David/PERSON angrily/O insults/O his/O boss/O and/O is/O fired/O ./O 
He/O coaxes/O his/O wife/O to/O quit/O her/O job/O as/O well/O and/O seek/O a/O new/O adventure/O ./O 
The/O Howards/O decide/O to/O liquidate/O their/O assets/O and/O drop/O out/O like/O in/O Easy/O Rider/O heading/O out/O to/O see/O the/O country/O in/O a/O Winnebago/O recreational/O vehicle/O ./O 
They/O leave/O LA/LOCATION with/O nest/O egg/O but/O don/O t/O get/O very/O far/O ./O 
The/O plan/O goes/O awry/O when/O Linda/PERSON loses/O nearly/O all/O their/O cash/O playing/O roulette/O at/O the/O Desert/LOCATION Inn/LOCATION Casino/LOCATION in/O Las/LOCATION Vegas/LOCATION ./O 
Out/O of/O money/O and/O with/O nowhere/O to/O go/O the/O couple/O ends/O up/O in/O Safford/LOCATION Arizona/LOCATION ./O 
David/PERSON unsuccessfully/O applies/O for/O a/O delivery/O job/O at/O a/O local/O pharmacy/O and/O resorts/O to/O an/O employment/O agency/O ./O 
Obnoxiously/O reminded/O by/O a/O counselor/O about/O being/O fired/O from/O his/O high/O paying/O job/O in/O advertising/O David/PERSON accepts/O the/O best/O position/O available/O as/O a/O crossing/O guard/O taunted/O by/O local/O school/O kids/O ./O 
Linda/PERSON meanwhile/O has/O found/O employment/O as/O the/O assistant/O manager/O at/O the/O local/O Der/ORGANIZATION Wienerschnitzel/ORGANIZATION working/O under/O a/O kid/O half/O her/O age/O ./O 
She/O and/O David/PERSON are/O living/O in/O a/O trailer/O park/O almost/O broke/O and/O now/O accountable/O to/O brats/O ./O 
Only/O a/O few/O days/O after/O beginning/O their/O pursuit/O of/O the/O dream/O of/O dropping/O out/O of/O society/O they/O decide/O that/O it/O is/O better/O to/O get/O back/O their/O old/O lifestyle/O as/O soon/O as/O possible/O ./O 
They/O point/O the/O Winnebago/O toward/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION where/O David/PERSON begs/O for/O his/O old/O job/O back/O ./O 
Estranged/O sisters/O Isobel/PERSON and/O Marion/PERSON are/O forced/O to/O reunite/O when/O their/O father/O dies/O and/O they/O must/O decide/O how/O to/O handle/O Katherine/PERSON their/O young/O alcoholic/O mentally/O unstable/O stepmother/O who/O has/O been/O left/O nothing/O but/O the/O rural/O home/O in/O which/O they/O were/O raised/O ./O 
Isobel/PERSON and/O her/O lover/O Patrick/PERSON own/O a/O small/O graphic/O design/O company/O that/O is/O struggling/O to/O stay/O afloat/O ./O 
Her/O sister/O suggests/O she/O and/O her/O born/O again/O Christian/O husband/O Tom/PERSON help/O them/O expand/O the/O business/O by/O finding/O investors/O and/O making/O Katherine/PERSON a/O partner/O responsible/O for/O finding/O new/O business/O ./O 
Isobel/PERSON has/O grave/O misgivings/O about/O the/O plan/O but/O finally/O agrees/O to/O it/O when/O Marion/PERSON convinces/O Patrick/PERSON of/O its/O potential/O success/O ./O 
Before/O long/O the/O strain/O of/O running/O the/O expanded/O business/O impacts/O Isobel/PERSON s/O relationship/O with/O Patrick/PERSON who/O is/O becoming/O increasingly/O dependent/O upon/O her/O while/O at/O the/O same/O time/O Katherine/PERSON s/O tenuous/O hold/O on/O sanity/O begins/O to/O unravel/O ./O 
Three/O Englishmen/O working/O as/O waiters/O on/O a/O cruise/O ship/O in/O 1/O 9/O 2/O 7/O are/O given/O a/O chance/O to/O work/O for/O the/O Al/ORGANIZATION Capone/ORGANIZATION gang/O ./O 
Another/O single/O shot/O Lumiere/ORGANIZATION Brothers/ORGANIZATION film/O this/O time/O showing/O the/O demolition/O of/O a/O wall/O in/O the/O grounds/O of/O the/O factory/O ./O 
A/O successful/O Wall/O Street/O trader/O returns/O to/O Britain/LOCATION with/O her/O family/O but/O her/O new/O home/O in/O the/O countryside/O contains/O a/O disturbing/O secret/O ./O 
Colleen/PERSON is/O the/O manager/O of/O a/O dress/O shop/O named/O The/O Ames/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION owned/O by/O Donald/PERSON Ames/PERSON ./O 
They/O try/O to/O keep/O Uncle/O Cedric/PERSON from/O working/O because/O he/O ll/O ruin/O the/O company/O ./O 
Troubles/O start/O when/O he/O hires/O schemer/O Joe/PERSON as/O his/O personal/O assistant/O ./O 
He/O later/O also/O hires/O Minnie/PERSON a/O woman/O who/O has/O a/O great/O passion/O for/O fashion/O ./O 
When/O he/O buys/O the/O dress/O shop/O for/O Minnie/PERSON where/O Colleen/PERSON works/O as/O a/O bookkeeper/O a/O scandal/O is/O soon/O followed/O ./O 
Donald/PERSON decides/O to/O shut/O the/O shop/O but/O is/O stopped/O because/O of/O his/O infatuation/O towards/O Colleen/PERSON ./O 
It/O is/O Colleen/PERSON who/O eventually/O makes/O a/O profit/O out/O of/O the/O things/O that/O happened/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O a/O man/O named/O Cedric/PERSON tries/O to/O adopt/O Minnie/PERSON ./O 
Minnie/PERSON refuses/O and/O thereby/O causes/O a/O scandel/O ./O 
